(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ここ聞き手
Listen here.
ここ聞き手皆さま、本日はですね
Everyone, listen here. Today...
スペシャルなゲストと一緒に
I'm doing a 3D collaboration stream
3Dコラボ配信をするちゅわよ
with a special guest.
ということで、早速ゲストお呼びしましょう
So, let's call our guest right away.
周防パトラちゃーん！
Suou Patra-chan!
こんばんわんわん
Good evening-wan-wan!
なんか思ってたんと違う、
This studio is a bit different
このスタジオ
from what I expected.
あの、なんですかこの巨大な耳？
Um, what is this giant ear?
きもいね
It's gross.
はい！こんばんわ元気にやらしてもらいましょー！
Yes! Good evening! Let's do this with energy!
はい！ということで改めまして周防パトラちゃんです！
Yes! So once again, here is Suou Patra-chan!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
Nice to meet you!
こんばんわんわん、周防パトラです！
Good evening-wan-wan, I'm Suou Patra!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
いや、ちょっとプロデューサーよくぞお越しくださいました
Wow, Producer, thank you so much for coming.
いやいやいや、こちらこそおかげで
No, no, no, the pleasure is mine.
さきほど、さきほどですねフブキちゃんの可愛いASMRをね
Just now, we were listening to Fubuki-chan's cute ASMR.
はい。もうプロデュースさせていただきましたけど
Yes, I've already produced it...
どうですか？どうですか？ご心服な
...but how was it? How was it? Are you impressed?
いやもう本当に、いやもうね、
Well, as some of you in the comments
みなさんでもう本当にねコメント欄もご存知の方もいらっしゃいますけども
already know, this time...
この度ね、あの
...this time...
パトラちゃんにパトラちゃんにプロデュースしていただいた
Shirakami Fubuki's ASMR voice pack,
白上フブキのASMRボイスが
produced by Patra-chan...
16時からね、発売となりましたー！
...has been on sale since 4:00 PM!
イエーイなのかな？
Is it a "Yay"?
え、なんか聞いたところによるとフブキちゃん久しぶりのボイス販売
I heard this is your first voice pack sale in a while, Fubuki-chan.
そうですね、本当に久しぶりのボイス販売で。それがしかもASMRってことでね
That's right, it really has been a while. And it's ASMR, too.
はい、しかもねパトラが台本を書いてパトラがね
Yes, and Patra wrote the script, and Patra...
色々ね、ディレクションしてパトラのスタジオでね、すごよね
Did the direction at Patra's studio. It's amazing!
でもう100%パトラちゃん仕様というか、ね。
It's 100% Patra-chan's style.
もう完全プロデュースで出させていただきましたけども
It was fully produced by her.
いやいやいや、もう何がすごいってあの覚えてるこのトッツ？
No, no, what's truly amazing is... do you remember that call-in?
みなさんあのトッツからさ、ここまでくると思わないって
Everyone, I bet you didn't think we'd come this far from that call-in.
ね、去年の2023年の6月
Right, June of last year, 2023.
のときに、なんかASMRの話になって、
We talked about ASMR back then,
まあまあ出せたらいいねぐらいの、さ、軽いノリだったにも関わらず
and it was just a casual 'it would be nice' thing, but...
ホロの運営...
Holo management...
そだね。
That's right.
うん。
Yeah.
その配信聞いてたらしくて。
Apparently they were listening to that stream.
すごかった。
It was amazing.
「やりましょう」みたいなことを言い始めてね。
They started saying things like, "Let's do it."
でマネージャーもね「やりましょう」とか言い始めて。
And the manager also started saying, "Let's do it."
「パトラさんに連絡しますね」って言われて「あ、ちょ、お、えっ？」みたいな。
I was told "I'll contact Patra-san," and I was like "Oh, wait, uh, what?"
そう、なんか、なんか急にさ。
Yeah, like, suddenly...
あの、そう、マネージャーさんから連絡来たから、パトラ「え、なんかやっちゃった？」と思って。
Um, yeah, the manager contacted me, so I thought, "Did I do something wrong?"
怒られる！と思ったら全然違ったね。
I thought I was going to get scolded! But it was completely different.
全然ね。
Completely.
全然ね、違いましたね。
Completely different, wasn't it?
いやー、本当になり、まさかこんなに早く実現するとは。
Man, really, I didn't think it would happen this fast.
1年も経ってないよ、だって。
I mean, it hasn't even been a year.
経ってない！
It hasn't!
経ってないよ。
It hasn't.
本当に爆速で何もかもが進みまして。
Everything proceeded at light speed.
いや、それでマネージャーに。
Yeah, and then I asked the manager...
うん。
Yeah.
なんかあの、「え、あの、好きに書いていいんですか？」って聞いたら。
Like, "Um, can I write whatever I want?"
「はい、大丈夫です」って言ったから。
And they said, "Yes, it's fine."
「あ、じゃあ、あの、えちくないように書きます」って言って。
So I said, "Oh, then I'll write it so it's not lewd."
それで書いたんだよ。
That's how I wrote it.
ほどよい感じのね。
A good balance, right?
そうそうそうそう。
Right, right, right, right.
ということで、マネコ...ボイスも発売しましたし。
Anyway, the Maneco... voice was released.
せっかくなんでね、3Dコラボもしちゃおうということでね。
And since we're at it, we decided to do a 3D collab.
パトラちゃんに本日ね、あの、ホロライブのスタジオにお越しいただいてるんですけど。
Patra-chan is here at the Hololive studio today, but...
ど、ど、ど...
How, how, how...
いやあのね、さっきからフブキちゃんの横にずっとベタベタしたいんだけど。
Well, I've wanted to be clingy with Fubuki-chan this whole time.
これがカオスすぎてさ。
But this place is just too chaotic.
これ、これ何？周りもちょっとカメラの引きございますかね？
This, what is this? Can we get a wide shot from the camera?
本当の、あの、ふざけんなって感じなんですけど。
It's really like, "Are you kidding me?"
キモ、キモい。
It's gross, it's gross.
なんかミッキーマウスみたいにさ、なんか出てればいいよねみたいな感じで入れちゃお。
I was like, "Let's put them in like Mickey Mouse, it'll be fine."
こんなん嫌でしょ、こんなマウス嫌でしょ。
You wouldn't want this, you wouldn't want this kind of mouse.
おかしいだろこの空間。
This space is weird.
どうなってるんだ！
What's going on!
ASMRするって聞いて、うわ、うわあー。
I heard we were doing ASMR, and whoa, whoa...
怖すぎ、ASMR怖すぎる。
Scary, ASMR is too scary.
風邪引いたときに見る悪夢やでこんなん。
This is like a nightmare you see when you have a cold.
可愛い空間作りますねって聞いてたんだけど。
I was told they were making a cute space.
これ、運営さん頑張ってくれたんですけど、前のめりすぎた結果。
The staff worked hard on this, but as a result of being too eager...
なんかね、27億円のスタジオ、こんなんなんか...
You know, the 27 billion yen studio, and it's like this...
申し訳なくなってくる。
I'm starting to feel bad.
そんなに本当は、もっといろんなステージあるんだけど。
Actually, there are so many other stages.
今回はね、この、あの、耳の森みたいな。
But this time, it's this, like, forest of ears.
耳の森だね。耳の森ですね。
A forest of ears. It's a forest of ears.
これ完全に悪夢なんですけど。
This is a complete nightmare.
まあ風邪引いたかなっていう。まあでもASMRということでね。
Maybe I have a cold. But anyway, since it's ASMR...
この、なんか耳だらけの空間になったんですけどね。本当にもう。
It became this space filled with ears. Honestly...
何を考えてるんですかね、スタッフさんはね。
What were the staff thinking?
あ、でもきっとこれで素敵なASMRを今から披露してくれる。
Ah, but I'm sure they'll perform wonderful ASMR now.
そ、そうだね。はい。
Th-That's right. Yes.
まあなんですけども、ここでパトラちゃん、いやもう偉大なね、プロデューサーパトラ様がですね。
But anyway, here Patra-chan, or rather, the great producer Patra-sama...
改めてどんな方なのか、ご紹介をしていこうかなと思いますので。
I'd like to introduce what kind of person you are once again.
そうで、パトラのこと知らない人も絶対いっぱいいると思うので。
That's right, I'm sure there are lots of people who don't know Patra.
改めてパトラちゃんのことを知ってほしいので、ちょっと白上準備行ってきますので。
I want people to get to know Patra-chan better, so Shirakami's going to go get ready.
あ、待ってください。
Ah, wait.
お、え、あ、よいしょ。行ってくるわ。
Oh, eh, ah, heave-ho. I'm going.
よいしょ。このカオスな空間で、しかもこの、たくさん見てる人数で繋げと。
Heave-ho. In this chaotic space, and with this many people watching, I have to fill the time.
あ、あ、だます、パトラです。えーと、独身です。
Ah, ah, damasu, I'm Patra. Um, I'm single.
えーと、えーと、えーと、あ、そう、えーと、かなたちゃんどうですか？パトラのこのボインボイン。
Um, um, um, ah, right, um, Kanata-chan, how is it? My bouncy breasts.
あの、貸してあげるけどどうかな？どうかな？
I'll let you borrow them, how about it? How about it?
ど、ど、よいしょ。え、これ、スタジオ破壊やんけ。
How, how, heave-ho. Wait, this is studio destruction.
大丈夫かな？大丈夫かな？
Is it okay? Is it okay?
先生見てないよね、大丈夫。
Sensei isn't watching, right? It's fine.
ということで、今日はね、フブキちゃんの、あの、一緒に、楽しいASMRを、たぶん、たぶんすると思うので。
So today, I'll probably, probably do a fun ASMR with Fubuki-chan.
あの、よろしくお願いします。
So, please look forward to it.
はーい、パトラちゃん。
Okay, Patra-chan.
はーい、お待たせしました。こちらへどうぞ。
Okay, sorry for the wait. Please come this way.
はーい。
Okay.
椅子にお座りください。
Please have a seat.
はーい。
Okay.
はい、ということでですね、ここからはですね、こちらの、周防パトラプロフィールを見ていこうと思います！
Yes, and so, from here, let's take a look at this Suou Patra Profile!
はい。なんかいろいろ、はてなだらけなんですけどもね。
Yes. It's full of question marks.
本当によく分かんないはてな、いっぱいあると思うんですけど。
I'm sure there are many mysterious question marks.
本当だね。
That's true.
何が書か、何が書かれているのかね。
I wonder what's wr- what's written there.
じゃあまずね、上4つちょっと見ていこうかなと思います。こちらです。
Well, first, let's look at the top four. Here they are.
はい。
Okay.
デデン！
Ta-da!
お、アピールポイントが「ASMRが得意でギターを弾くアニメ声の女。ゲームはジャンル問わず何でも大好き！」
Oh, the appeal point is "A girl with an anime voice who is good at ASMR and plays guitar. Loves games of all genres!"
うん、何でも好きです。
Yeah, I love everything.
いや、本当に何でもやってるよね、パトラちゃんね。
Yeah, you really do everything, don't you, Patra-chan?
何でもやってます。ゲーム大好き。
I do everything. I love games.
いや、さすがでございますわ。そして、チャームポイントは？
No, as expected. And what's the charm point?
チャームポイントはこの、あの、最初ね、ちょっと「ボイン」って書こうとしたんですけど。
The charm point is this, um, at first, I was going to write "boin"...
ま、ね、あの、外部だし、と思って、アポロ、っていう、このお団子にしました。
But, you know, since it's an outside collab, I went with these Apollo-shaped buns.
どうですか？
How is it?
あ、可愛い。
Ah, cute.
ぶっ刺すよ。
I'll stab you with them.
いや、ぶっ刺す怖いな。
Whoa, "stab you" is scary.
だはは。
Dahaha.
凶器にしないでくださいな。
Please don't use them as weapons.
はいはい。そしてそして、得意なことがこちら。デデン！「ASMR」ということでね。
Yes, yes. And next, the thing she's good at is here. Ta-da! "ASMR".
やっぱり、今日はね、これを書かせていただきたいと、思いますよ。
After all, I wanted to write this for today.
いやもう、パトラちゃんと言ったらもうASMR、もう、素晴らしいですから、本当に。
Well, when you think of Patra-chan, you think of ASMR, it's really wonderful.
いや、もうパトラね、ASMRが好きすぎて、あの、スタジオを建てたんです。
Well, Patra loves ASMR so much that I built a studio.
スタジオも建てて。
Built a studio too.
そう、台本も書いて。台本もね、書きましたね。
Yeah, and wrote scripts. I wrote scripts too.
ね、さっき聞いたんですけど、白上のさ、そのボイスの収録とかも、効果音とかも全部ね、そう、パトラちゃん監修してくれたってことなんですけど。
Right, I heard earlier that Patra-chan supervised Shirakami's voice recordings and all the sound effects.
はいはい。
Yes, yes.
焚き火の音がさ、ガチの焚き火音ってちょっと。
The campfire sound was like a real campfire sound...
あ、はいはい。いろいろね、やっちゃったかな。そうなんですよ。
Ah, yes. I guess I did various things. That's right.
周防パトラ プロフィール
Suou Patra Profile
焚き火の音もガチの...
The sound of the bonfire is also real...
...方の音？
...real nature sounds?
そうそうそう。
Right, right.
火の音とかということで、
With the fire sounds and all,
もう深夜にね、撮りました。
I recorded them late at night.
すごい！
Amazing!
山の中行って、パチパチパチパチ...
I went into the mountains and... crackle, crackle...
ええ！？山の中で！？
Wait, in the mountains!?
そうだね。あと靴の音とかも...
Yeah. And even the sound of shoes...
うんうん。
Uh-huh.
もう、あと何だろうな...
Also, let's see...
聴いてる方が「おれくん」もいると思うんだけど、
I know there are some "Ore-kuns" listening,
ちょっと「おれくん」目線にしたいなって思って、
and I wanted it to be from the "Ore-kun" perspective,
こう男性用の靴を買って、
so I bought some men's shoes,
ドスッ、ドスッ、ドスッて作りましたね。
and made thudding sounds like "clomp, clomp, clomp."
すごいこだわりだ...
That's incredible dedication...
いや、本当にね、ASMRに命を懸けてくださっている。
Truly, she's putting her life into ASMR.
はい。
Yes.
あ、あと、あとフブキちゃんの耳をモフモフできるんですよ、あの音声。
Oh, and also, that audio lets you fluff Fubuki-chan's ears.
うわぁ！もうそれはね...
Whoa! That's just...
それで、あのフブキちゃんが照れてる...
And then, Fubuki-chan gets all embarrassed...
あ、そう、そういう顔をね、ナデナデしちゃうぞみたいなね、
Yeah, like that, like "I'm gonna pet that face of yours."
やつが入ってるんでね。
There's a track like that in there.
いやぁ、やばいっすね。良くないですよ、ホント。
Man, that's intense. Not good for the heart, really.
ここも聞きどころです。聞きどころです。
That's definitely a highlight. A must-listen.
じゃあ次行きますか。満足です。
Shall we move on? I'm satisfied.
満足するな！満足するな！
Don't be satisfied yet! Don't stop there!
そして苦手なことがこれ、どういうことですか？
And then, what's this about "things you're bad at"?
えっと、なんか料理すると道具が壊れる？
Uh, "breaking tools whenever you cook"?
呪われてるんです、パトラ。
I'm cursed, Fubuki.
なんで呪われてるの！？
Why are you cursed!?
何故か料理すると、道具がその場で壊れるんですよね。
For some reason, tools just break on the spot when I cook.
生配信でもミキサー壊したり、まあすごいんですよね。
I've even broken a mixer during a stream. It's crazy.
なんか呪われてるのかもしれない。
Maybe I really am cursed.
電化製品か何かに呪われてる、家電に呪われてる？
Cursed by electronics or something? An appliance curse?
そうなの。そうなの。
Exactly. That's it.
料理対決とかあったらマジ、
If there's ever a cooking battle,
敵の方にパトラ送ったほうがいいかも。
it's probably best to send me to the enemy's side.
破壊してくれる。ちゃんとやれる。
I'll sabotage them. I'll get it done.
マジか！それはそれでどうかなと思いますけど、じゃあまだ隠れてるところございますので見ていきましょう。こちらです。
Seriously!? I'm not sure about that, but let's see what else is hidden. Here we go.
はい！
Okay!
お！最近ハマっているもの。
Oh! "Things you've been into lately."
レトロゲームや90年代のアニメ。これ、この間、あれでしょ。
Retro games and 90s anime. You played that the other day, right?
「ちびまる子ちゃん」のゲームやってたもんね。
You were playing a "Chibi Maruko-chan" game.
そう。なんか正月から賭博をちょっと... 賭博... やったりとか。
Yeah. I was doing a bit of... gambling... since New Year's.
おお、なるほど。レトロゲームすごいハマってて。
Oh, I see. You're really into retro games.
やってるよね、本当に。「ファイナルファンタジー」とか。
You really are. Like "Final Fantasy" and stuff.
あ、やってたね。そう。1からね、ずっとやってて。
Oh, you did. Yeah. I've been playing them from the first one.
おお、素晴らしい。素晴らしい。だったり、その影響とか、あと最近なんかNetflixとか映画とかで、
That's wonderful. And because of that, or recently on Netflix and movies,
あの「幽☆遊☆白書」とか...
like "YuYu Hakusho" and...
あ、やってるね！そう。あと「スラムダンク」とかあるから、ちょっと昔のアニメをね、
Oh, they have those! Yeah. Also "Slam Dunk," so I've been watching old anime,
結構見たりとかしてて、90年代ぐらいにハマってる。
watching quite a bit of it, getting into the 90s era.
おお、いいですね。どうですか、フブキちゃんは何かしてたりします？
Oh, that's nice. How about you, Fubuki-chan? Been into anything?
え？何だろう、最近ハマってるものか。
Eh? What would it be... things I'm into lately...
最近何にハマってるかな。むしろ探してる途中かも。
I wonder. Maybe I'm still in the middle of looking for something.
探してる！？
Looking for something!?
なんかね、前はいろいろなこうね、賭け事とかも好きっちゃ好きなんですけども、
Well, before, I used to like various kinds of gambling and such,
なんかね、もっとハマれるものないかなって。ちょっと前まではなんか自分でぬいぐるみ作ったりとか...
but I was wondering if there's something else I can get into. Until recently, I was making my own plushies...
え、すごい！推しぬい！そうそう、とか作ってたりしたんだけども、
Whoa, amazing! Oshi-nui! Yeah, I was making those, but...
ちょっと2024年、ちょっとまた欲しいなと、新たな趣味が。
In 2024, I think I want a new hobby.
わぁ、考えておきます。なるほどなるほど。そして何フェチ？これですね。
Wow, I'll think about it. I see. And then, "What fetish?" This one.
あ、これ。妹フェチ。
Oh, this. "Little sister fetish."
妹フェチ！？はい、妹フェチ。
Little sister fetish!? Yes, little sister fetish.
ホロライブの中の妹ポジションの方お待ちしております。
I'm waiting for those in the little sister position in Hololive.
既にちょっと妹になりそうなホロメンいますか？今んとこ。言っちゃっていいですか？いいですよ、どうぞ。
Are there any Holomem who seem likely to be your sister? So far. Can I say it? Yes, go ahead.
え、まずフワモコちゃん！フワモコちゃんね！
First, FuwaMoco-chan! Ah, FuwaMoco-chan!
え、いっぱいすぎて、ラプちゃん！ラプちゃんはちょっとあの、クソガキ感ありますけどいいですか？
There's too many... Lap-chan! Lap-chan has that "bratty kid" vibe, is that okay?
あ、もうそれがいいんですよ！ザコとか言ってほしいよね！
Oh, that's exactly why she's good! I want her to call me "weakling"!
あ、それから、えっと、かなたんも可愛いし！かなたんも妹。なるほど。
And then, Kanatan is also cute! Kanatan as a sister. I see.
あ、でもぜ、あ、何、えーっと... ホロ可愛い子多いからですね、ちょっと...
But... what... well, there are so many cute girls in Hololive, so...
ちょっとあと5時間悩んでいいですか。悩みすぎや！悩みすぎや！
Can I have another five hours to think? You're overthinking it! Way too much!
あ、でもね、そして、ちょっと次行きますか。これ、将来の夢なんです。夢です。
Well anyway, shall we move on? This is your future dream. A dream.
はい、夢です。35年ローンを返す。
Yes, a dream. "Paying off my 35-year loan."
35年ローンってすごいんですよ。なんで35年...
A 35-year loan is huge. Why 35 years...
返すと増える。すごいよ。返すと増える。これ何で35年ローンが組まれてるんですかね？
When I pay it off, it increases. It's crazy. It just keeps growing. Why do you have a 35-year loan anyway?
いや、あれなんですよ。スタジオを建てて35年ローン組んで、
Well, here's the thing. I built a studio with a 35-year loan,
返すじゃないですか、ちょこまかちょこまか。そうすると「あ、また改造しよう」ってなって、
and as I'm paying it back little by little, I'm like, "Oh, let's upgrade it again."
また改造して増えるんですよ。
So I renovate, and the loan increases.
あ、だから35年に留まらないみたいなところなの？もしからすると。あ、でもオーバーはしてないんだけどね、
So it's like it'll never actually end at 35 years? Possibly. Well, I'm not going over the limit,
なんかどんどん増えてておかしいな。おかしいな。いついつこれ返し終わるんですか？
but it just keeps growing and it's weird. It's so strange. When will you ever finish paying it off?
ねぇ。そうなんです。だからあと35年は配信するからよろしくね！
Who knows? That's how it is. So I'll be streaming for another 35 years, stick with me!
すごいな、これ。じゃあ今年の夏ぐらいになると...
That's incredible. So by the time this summer comes around...
周防パトラ プロフィール
Suou Patra Profile
35年とかになってそうで、
It looks like it'll be around 35 years,
怖いね、これ。怖いわ。
so that's scary. It's scary.
ホロライブさん、案件お待ちしてます。
Hololive-san, I'm waiting for job offers.
やばい、どんどんスタジオが強化されていく。
Oh no, the studio is getting reinforced more and more.
そして、そして。こちらが、
And then, and then. This here,
これがなんだ... これは何だ？
what is this... what is this?
白上フブキの印象は？
What's the impression of Shirakami Fubuki?
ま、これはね... はいはい。
Well, this... Yeah, yeah.
パトラ以外のファンも全員思ってる。
All the fans besides Patra think so too.
何人いるんですか？！
How many of you are there?!
一人ですよ！
I'm just one person!
白上フブキは一人ですよ、一人。
Shirakami Fubuki is just one person, one.
一人ください！
Give me one!
5人ぐらいなんかいるみたいな、
Like there are about five of you,
AIがいるとか言われますけども。
or that there's an AI, so they say.
一人ですよ、一人！
I'm just one person, one!
いや、白上フブキは一人ですよ。
No, Shirakami Fubuki is one person.
いっぱいいるよね？
There are many, right?
いません、一人ですよ。
No, it's just one person.
常にあのXやってる白上フブキと、
The Shirakami Fubuki who's always on X,
確かに。
True.
常にあの配信してる白上フブキと、
the Shirakami Fubuki who's always streaming,
確かに。
True.
収録してる白上フブキ。
and the Shirakami Fubuki who's recording.
さあ、いっぱいいた、実は。
So, there were many, actually.
いっぱいいる、いっぱい。
There are many, many.
控えたんですか？
Did you hold back?
知らない間に増えている。
They increased without me knowing.
5人はいるって言われてますけどね。
It's said there are five of you.
あ、一人ですからね。
Ah, I'm just one person.
いつの間に増えてたんだろう、白上。
I wonder when I increased.
そしてそして、はい、最後。
And then, and then, yes, the last one.
なんかすごいビックに隠されているんですけど。
It's hidden by something really big.
そうじゃん、なんなのこれ。
Right, what is this.
これなんなんでしょうね、じゃ、こちらです。
I wonder what it is. Well, here it is.
どうぞ！ これなんですか？
Go ahead! What is this?
好きな食べ物
Favorite food
かにかまプリン
Crab stick pudding
あ、好きな食べ物。かにかまプリン！
Ah, favorite food. Crab stick pudding!
え、これ。これさ、
Wait, this. This,
ホロライブ、天下のホロライブ様に行くからさ...
since I'm going to Hololive, the great Hololive-sama...
気を使ってカレーって書いたんですけど、
I was being considerate and wrote "curry",
かにかまプリンに変わってて...
but it changed to crab stick pudding...
本当はかにかまプリンだけど、
It's actually crab stick pudding, but
ホロライブ来るからカレーにしてくれた...
since she's coming to Hololive, she made it curry...
そう、カレーに、あのね、乙女ぶってたら、書き換えられとり。
Yeah, to curry, you know, I was acting like a lady, but it got rewritten.
え、これスタッフさんの中にパトラオタクがいるってこと？
Wait, does this mean there's a Patra-otaku among the staff?
そういうこと。
That's what it means.
これはきっとよそ行きの回答だったということで、
This must be since it was a "public-facing" answer,
しっかり直されてます。
it's been properly corrected.
かにかまプリンが好きということで。
So you like crab stick pudding.
ほら、かにかまプリンってどんな、美味しいんですかこれ？
See, crab stick pudding... what's it like? Is it delicious?
いや、これは美味しいので、今日ホロライブの
No, it's delicious, so earlier I borrowed
スタジオのあのキッチンを先ほどお借りしまして。
the kitchen in the Hololive studio.
ほら、さっきトイレ行くって言ってさ、
Remember earlier when I said I was going to the toilet
なかなか戻ってこなかった時にパトラ作ってきました。
and didn't come back for a while? Patra was making it then.
作ってきた？！
You made it?!
そう。
Yes.
え、でも壊してない？ 本当に壊れてない？
Wait, but did you break anything? Really, it's not broken?
壊れてない。本当に？
It's not broken. "Really?"
奇跡！ 奇跡。
A miracle! A miracle.
良かった、良かった。え、じゃ食べれるってこと？
Thank goodness, thank goodness. Wait, so we can eat it?
今日は食べれますよ。
You can eat it today.
えー、じゃ、ちょっと用意していただきましょうか。
Whoa, then let's have it prepared.
はい。
Yes.
えー、ちょっとじゃ白上もちょっと座るか。これ出てくるのか？
Well then, I'll sit down too. Is it coming out?
いや、これはすごいですよ。
No, this is amazing.
えー、じゃちょっと棒を置いておこうかな、じゃ。よいしょ。
Well, I'll just put the stick down. Heave-ho.
あのラジオの企画やったんですけど、
I did a radio project,
その時のゲスト、加瀬さんに、おい、ラスティ、
the guest then, Kase-san... hey, Rusty...
アーマードコアのラスティ役の加瀬さんに。
Kase-san who played Rusty in Armored Core.
はい、加瀬さん。
Yes, Kase-san.
食べていただいた、加瀬さんにも食べさせたのこれ！
I had him eat it... You made Kase-san eat this too?!
ね、これ何これすごい。
Man, what is this, it's incredible.
プリンにさ、これ、めっちゃ見えるし、このプリン！
On the pudding... you can see it so well, this pudding!
がしゃん！ がしゃん！ うわ、すごい入れりょ、これ。
*Clang!* *Clang!* Whoa, that's a lot of stuffing.
ぷるぷるしてる。
It's wobbling.
めっちゃぷるぷるしてきた、かにかま。
The crab sticks are wobbling a lot.
これぐらいの、なんか太鼓したくなるね、いろいろ。
This much... makes me want to use it like a drum.
やめてやめてやめて。太鼓するな、太鼓するな。
Stop, stop, stop. Don't drum on it.
ぷるぷる。なにこれすごい。
Wobble, wobble. What is this, it's amazing.
え、これはどんな味がするんだ？
Wait, what does this taste like?
いや、これは、これはもう美味しい。
No, this... this is just delicious.
あの食べ方はダメだ、ことないよ。
That way of eating is not... no, that's not it.
両方一緒に食べるのが、ポイントですね、これは。
Eating both together is the key point here.
これ、どっちも白上好きなんだけど、
I like both of these, but
一緒に食べることでどんな化学反応が起こるのか。
what kind of chemical reaction happens when you eat them together.
プリンが好きなのと、
I like pudding, and
ま、カニが食べれないから、かにかまをよく食べてたんだけど。
well, since I can't eat real crab, I used to eat crab sticks often.
なるほどね、好きなもの一緒に食べたら、
I see. If you eat things you like together,
めちゃくちゃ美味しいみたい。
it's apparently super delicious.
え、なんか甘いし、ちょっとしょっぱい感じなの？
Wait, so it's sweet and a bit salty?
そう、それがね、ちょうどいいんだよね。
Yeah, that's what makes it just right.
ね、これガチガチに固まっているもん、かにかま。
Look, the crab sticks are packed in tight.
え、これ一緒に食べましょう、フブキちゃん。
Let's eat this together, Fubuki-chan.
一緒に食べますかな。はい。じゃ行きましょうかな。
Shall we eat together? Okay. Let's do it.
じゃ、いただきます。
Okay, let's eat.
いただきます。いただきます。
Let's eat. Let's eat.
うーん！ うーん！
Mmm! Mmm!
デリシャス！
Delicious!
なんかなんだか、とってもデリシャス！
Somehow, it's really delicious!
不思議な感じが。不思議な感じがしますね。
A strange feeling. I get a strange feeling.
あ、どうしたの？ もっと。あ、そうそうそう、そうやって混ぜてバクっとね。
Oh, what's wrong? More. Ah, yeah, yeah, mix it like that and take a big bite.
じゃ、一緒にこれね、一本丸々じゃ、あー。
Then, together... a whole one... ahh.
あ、そう。いいですね。
Ah, right. That's good.
なんか固まってるね、どうしたの？
You've frozen up, what happened?
あ、いい笑顔。
Ah, what a good smile.
やっぱね、新年あけおめと言えば、かにかまプリンだよね。
As expected, when you think of New Year's greetings, you think of crab stick pudding.
わかる。あ、スタッフさんの分も作った... なんで逃げるんですか？
I get it. Ah, I made some for the staff too... Why are you running away?
やめてください！ そうそうそう、それです。
Please stop! Yeah, yeah, that's it.
はい、よかったら食べてください。誰も食べないのなんで？
Here, please eat some if you'd like. Why is nobody eating it?
あ、フブキちゃんいっぱい食べてくれて。フブキちゃんいっぱいあるからね。
Ah, Fubuki-chan is eating a lot. There's plenty for you, Fubuki-chan.
あ、どうしたの？ どうしたの？
Oh, what's wrong? What's wrong?
トゥルトゥルな中にさ、モサモサがいる。
Inside the smooth texture, there's something fuzzy.
あ、かにかまのモサモサ。新種発見って感じだよね。
Ah, the fuzziness of the crab stick. It's like a new species discovery.
なんか、すごい新食感。わかるわかる。
It's a really new texture. I get it, I get it.
トゥルトゥルだけどモサモサ。わかる。
Smooth but fuzzy. I get it.
それがいいんだよね、なんか。アンバランスな感じ。
That's what's good about it. That unbalanced feeling.
うわ...
Whoa...
すごいアンバランス！
Such a strange balance!
イェーイ！
Yay!
美味しいでしょ？
Tastes good, right?
ま...まずくはないよ、もちろんね！
W-well, it's not bad, of course!
どっちも美味しいからさ。
Both parts are delicious on their own.
でもさ、食感が迷子になるのよ！
But the texture is all over the place!
食感...まぁちょっとしょっぱいからね。
The texture... well, it is a bit salty.
そうそうそうそう。
Right, right, right, right.
わかる、わかるよ、わかる。
I get it, I totally get it.
うん、本当にまずくはないんだけど...
Yeah, it really doesn't taste bad, but...
このプリンのトゥルトゥルと、
the slipperiness of the pudding...
カニカマのこの繊維っていうのかな？
and the fibers of the crab sticks...
これが、あのトゥルトゥルモサモサ...
It's like, slippery and fluffy...
わかる。まぁね、最初はそうくるかもしれないけど、
I know. Well, it might feel that way at first,
だんだん癖になるみたいな。
but you'll eventually get addicted to it.
これが癖になっていく！そうそうそうそう。
It starts to grow on you! Right, right.
でもプリンはプリン、カニカマはカニカマで食べたいよ！
But I want to eat pudding as pudding and crab sticks as crab sticks!
そんな本音を...！
How could you say that...!
おいしいおいしい。
It's good, it's good.
いや本当に美味しいんだよ。
No, it's really delicious.
そうでしょ？
Right?
でも口の中でモサモサするしトゥルトゥルするし...
But it's fluffy and slippery in my mouth...
あ、やっぱりコメントも「俺も食べたい」「私も食べたい」！
Ah, the comments say "I want to eat it too" and "Me too"!
フブちゃんいいなー、ほらね！いっぱい見えてるよ。
See, Fubu-chan? Everyone's jealous!
うわぁ...！でもちょっと一回経験はしてほしい、本当に！
Whoa...! But I really want you all to try it once!
うん。まずいとかは全然ない、むしろ美味しいんだけどさ、
Yeah. It's not bad at all, it's actually tasty,
口の中が何とも言えない感じになる！本当に。うん。
but the feeling in your mouth is just indescribable! Truly.
そう、トゥルトゥルモサモサ。
Yeah, slippery and fluffy.
それはつまりハマっちゃったってことよ！やっぱりね！
That means you've fallen for it! I knew it!
そういうこと。わかる、わかる。
That's how it is. I get it.
まぁ何か癖にはなるかもしれない。「何だこれ？」っていう。
Well, it might become a habit. Like, "What is this?"
あ、やっぱりコメントも「え、俺も食べたい」って。あ、ね、分かってる分かってる。
Oh, more comments saying "I want to eat it too." See, I told you.
いや、ゴミじゃねえかよ！
Wait, it looks like trash!
配信終わったら届けに行くわ、みんなに。待ってて。
I'll deliver some to everyone after the stream. Just wait.
うわぁ！でも美味しい。美味しい。
Whoa! But it's good. It's good.
プリンも美味しいね。美味しい。
The pudding is good too. Tasty.
いや何かな、今日ASMRコラボって聞いてきたのに何でカニカマ食べてんの...
I mean, I came here for an ASMR collab, so why am I eating crab sticks...
本当にカニカマとプリンを食べるっていう。
Literally just eating crab sticks and pudding.
多分数分、俺たちは何を見せられてるんだ...てかこれすごいね！
Everyone's probably like, "What are we watching..." But this is amazing!
すごいプルプルだよ！
It's so jiggly!
このために作ったんかい！って。
Did you make it just for this?!
このためにご用意しましただよ。
I prepared it just for this.
いや凄いわ。他どこで使うんだ、これ。カニカマプリン。
Unbelievable. Where else would you use this? Crab stick pudding.
え、これはもう何か、ホロメンの何か...
Oh, this could be like, for the Hololive members...
あの、ホロライブの罰ゲームでも使って。
...yeah, use it for a Hololive penalty game.
パトちゃんの好物を罰ゲームにするんじゃない！
Don't turn Patra-chan's favorite food into a penalty!
いいよいいよ、私は汚れでも何でもやるよ。
It's fine, it's fine. I'll do the dirty work, or anything.
汚れって言うな！やだ、そんな。
Don't call it dirty work! Oh, stop it.
罰ゲームにカニカマプリンって。
Crab stick pudding for a penalty game...
でも普通に美味しいからな。
But it actually tastes good.
それかENの子が、日本に来たときに、
Or when the EN girls come to Japan,
「これが日本の伝統料理やで」つってバーンってね。
tell them "This is a traditional Japanese dish" and present it!
それはちょっと試してみたい！
I'd actually love to try that!
「これが、あの日本のとある地方のあれです」みたいな。食べさせてどう反応するかね。
"This is a dish from a certain region in Japan." Let's see how they react.
だね、それはちょっとやってみたいな。
Yeah, I'd like to see that.
じゃあフワモコちゃんあたりにやらせるか。
Let's have Fuwamoco-chan do it then.
バウバウ！モサモサする！って。
"Bau bau! It's so fluffy!"
モサモサする、美味しいけど！って。
"It's fluffy, but delicious!"
きっと良いコメント残してくれそうだな。嬉しいな。
I'm sure they'd leave some great comments. That'd be nice.
うーん、うまい。
Mm, tasty.
ところでまったり、カニカマプリン食べてるだけでいいのかしら？
By the way, is it okay if we just keep eating this crab stick pudding?
こんな豪華なお耳のスタジオに来て。
Coming to this luxurious ear-themed studio...
本当だよ、美味しいよ。
Indeed, it's delicious.
ほら、今回ボイス収録についてお話しくださいって書いてあるんですけど。
Look, it says here that we should talk about the voice recording.
今回のボイス収録、話すんですか？
Are we going to talk about the recording?
話しましょうにゃ、みんな気になってる、いつの間に撮ってたのって。
Let's talk about it. Everyone's wondering when we recorded it.
そうだね、もう本当に...
Right, it was really...
爆速で決まって！
...decided in a flash!
あの配信の後、本当に速攻決まって「やりましょう」ってなって。
Right after that stream, it was decided immediately to just do it.
そう、白上の耳には多分一週間ぐらいしてから、運営さんから「やりまーす」って連絡来て。
Yeah, like a week later, management told me, "We're doing it!"
ええ？！行動力早すぎやろ！って。
I was like, "What?! That was so fast!"
早かったね。そっからパトちゃん、本当に爆速で台本を作って動いてくれて。
It was fast. And then Patra-chan made the script and got moving really quickly.
で台本、うおーってなって。
I was so impressed by the script.
もうさ、あの、ASMRやるのはいいんだけどさ、
I mean, doing the ASMR was fine, but...
パトちゃん家に行って、パトちゃんが聞いてる前でやるの本当に恥ずかしくて！
...going to Patra's house and doing it in front of her while she listened was so embarrassing!
え、でも本当に恥ずかしかった。
It really was embarrassing.
お前らもやってるから、あとなんか「もう少しくらいのこの声で」とか。
You guys do it too. And I'd give directions like, "A bit more with this voice."
「このぐらいの感じで」っていう表現をパトラが堂々とやれば、そんなに恥ずかしくないかなと思って。
I thought if I acted confidently while saying things like "Keep it like this," it wouldn't be so embarrassing.
いやもう、本当に色んな指示をいただきました、収録中。うん。
Man, she gave me so many instructions during the recording. Yeah.
...そう、もうこんな感じで、とか...
...Yeah, like this, and so on...
すごかったよ、本当に。台本もすぐ提出して。
It was amazing, really. You submitted the script right away.
NGないでしょうかって言ったら、
When I asked if there were any issues,
多分フブキちゃんに確認してるかわかんないけど、大丈夫ですって言われて。
I'm not sure if they checked with you, but they said it was fine.
大丈夫ですって来た。
I got the "it's okay" message.
もうね、何も、何も悪いとこはなかった。めちゃめちゃ良かった。
There was absolutely nothing wrong with it. It was so good.
良かった。
I'm glad.
で、ね。もうそれで収録をしに行ってね。もう本当に恥ずかしくて恥ずかしくて。
And then, I went to record it. It was so incredibly embarrassing.
恥ずかしかったの？
Was it embarrassing?
めっちゃ恥ずかしかったよ！全然堂々と、なんかやり慣れた白上フブキですみたいな感じだったけど、
It was super embarrassing! I acted like a professional, but inside...
覚悟は決めてたけどね。もうね、あーもうここの、
I had steeled myself, though. Once I stepped into...
ここのもう収録ブースに入ってしまったら、もう覚悟を決めねばならぬ。本当にやるんだっていうことで。
...the recording booth, I knew I had to go through with it. Like, "I'm really doing this."
えー、上手かったよ。
Well, you were very good at it.
いやー、上手かったかなー？いや本当にもう必死すぎて、もう、恐縮でございます。
I wonder... I was just so desperate. I'm honored you think so.
いや、もうなんかいろんなテイクをいただいたりとか。
No, you gave me so many different takes.
そうそうそう。ちょっと、なんか、多分、恥ずかしいかもしれないけど、
Right, right. I thought it might be embarrassing, but...
ちょっとここら辺、吐息っぽい、なんか情熱っぽいのも長めにくださいって言って。
...I asked for longer takes of the breathy, passionate parts.
あ、わかりましたって感じでやってくれたから。
And you were like, "Oh, okay," and did it for me.
いや、もう怖い、怖い。あー、本当に恥ずかしい。恥ずかしい。
No, it's scary, scary. Ah, it's so embarrassing. So embarrassing.
いや、すごい良かったなって思ったな。
I thought it was really great.
いや、なんか、ASMRをやっぱり収録してる人ってすごいなって改めて思った。
It made me realize once again how amazing ASMR artists are.
こんな恥ずかしい思いをしながら収録してるのかと思うと、本当にもう。
Thinking that they record while feeling this embarrassed, it's truly something.
いやいや、何を。すこん部たちが喜んでいますよ。
No, no, what are you saying? The Sconbu are delighted.
お喜びいただければ嬉しいですけどもね。あのね、この台本書くときに、
I'm glad if they're happy. You know, when I was writing this script...
はいはい。すこん部の気持ちになろうと思って、
Yes, yes. I tried to put myself in the Sconbu's shoes,
あの、フブキちゃんのリスナーさん何人かウォッチして、それで配信も見て、
so I watched a few of your listeners and your streams,
はい！と思って書いたの。
and then I wrote it with a "Yes!" feeling.
うわ、見られている。見られている。
Whoa, we're being watched. We're being watched.
みんな調査対象にされているぞ、みんな！
Everyone, we're all subjects of her research!
だからあのクオリティというか、みんながね、本当欲しい多分セリフとか、
That's why it turned out so high-quality, with all the lines...
やって欲しいこと全部詰め込まれている感じで。
...and things everyone probably wants to hear packed into it.
もう本当にもう。うわ、これはパトラやべーなって。
Really... I was like, "Whoa, Patra is incredible."
パトラが書けば許してくれるかなと思って。
I figured they'd forgive me if Patra wrote it.
みんな許してくれてる。ありがたいよね、本当に。
Everyone is forgiving you. It's really helpful.
あんなセリフなかなかない、白上さんなかなかやんないからさ。
Lines like those are rare since you don't usually do that stuff.
はいはいはい。本当ドキドキしたよね、そう。
Right, right. It really made my heart race.
でもASMRといえば、パトラ一回あの、フブキちゃんの前に
But speaking of ASMR, before your turn, Patra...
スバルちゃんに妹系の台本もプロデュースしたことがあって。
...once produced a sister-type script for Subaru-chan too.
そう。それもあったから、
Yeah. Because of that experience,
フブキちゃんバージョンちょっと楽しみだったんよ、かなり。
I was really looking forward to your version.
いやーもう本当にありがとうございます。こうやって本当にできて良かった。
Well, thank you so much. I'm glad it turned out well.
良かったけども、もう、今回だけでいいよ、白上はもう。
I'm glad, but once is enough for me.
あ、好評だったらね。どうなるかわかんないけどね。
Well, if it's popular... you never know.
確かに。
True.
運営さんに、フブキさんもう一回やりましょうって来るかもしれん。
The staff might tell me, "Fubuki-san, let's do it again."
いや、他のホロメンでいいじゃないか！パトラ！
No, just do it with other Holomem! Patra!
えー、ブラックフブキ書いてないもん。
But I haven't written Black Fubuki yet.
何これ！？
What is this!?
何それ！？ブラックフブキまだ書いてない。
What's that!? I haven't written Black Fubuki yet.
やだ、やめろ。やめろ。ブラックバージョンのイヤホン出したんだからいいだろ！
No, stop it. You released Black version earphones, so it's fine!
あ、そういうこと。ブラックで聞けってこと？
Oh, I see. You mean listen to it in Black mode?
そうそうそう。あ、でもなんか結構ね、
Right, right. But actually,
最近すごい、白上にチクチク言葉を言われて喜ぶ人が多いんだよね。
lately there are many people who enjoy being told stinging words by Shirakami.
すごいわかる。「なんでや」みたいな。チクチク言葉やぞ、みたいな。
I totally get it. Like, "Wait, why?" even though it's stinging words.
いやいやいやと。なんかそういうちょっとチクチク言葉ASMRが欲しいらしくて。
No, no, no. Apparently, they want that kind of stinging words ASMR.
はいはい。それと思いながらも、最近ちょっとね、
Yes, yes. Thinking that, lately,
そういうの流行ってるというか、聞きたいみたいな人結構いるんだよ。
that's been trending, or rather, there are quite a few people who want to hear it.
おかしいって、皆さん。チクチク言葉で、心傷つくで。
You guys are weird. Stinging words hurt your heart, you know.
まあそれを乗り越えた先に何かが待っている、みたいなね。何が待っているの！？
Well, it's like something's waiting beyond that pain. Like what!?
我々鍛えられてますから。まあまあまあ、できたらね。
We've been trained, after all. Well, if I can...
できたらね、そこはね。
...if I can, then maybe.
はい、じゃあ次ブラックフブキでお願いします。運営さん本当動いちゃうから。
Okay, then Black Fubuki next, please. The staff will really make it happen.
ダメです。ダメダメ。
No way. No, no, no.
はい。ということで、ここまで楽しくお話ししてきましたけどね。
Right. We've had a fun talk up to this point.
ま、せっかくパトラちゃんが来てくれてるので、
Well, since Patra-chan is here,
ASMRにまつわるお遊びができたらなと思っております。
I thought we could play a little game related to ASMR.
お！やっと、なんか、この耳が活かされる感じかもしれんね。
Oh! Finally, it seems these ears of mine will be put to good use.
はい。じゃあね、またまた、ちょっと白上準備してきますので、パトラちゃんもちょっと立ってもらって、繋いどいてください。
Okay then, I'll go prepare. Patra-chan, please stand up and keep the viewers entertained.
はい、わかりました。じゃあ行ってきまーす。
Okay, I got it. See you later!
いや、ちょっとブラックフブキマジでいいと思わない？でもさ、さっき罵倒系って来たけど、
Honestly, don't you think Black Fubuki would be amazing? Earlier, people suggested a verbal abuse theme...
セクシーお姉さんっぽくしようかなと思ったけど、いや、解釈違いかな？どう思う？
...but I was thinking of doing a sexy older sister vibe. Or would that be out of character? What do you think?
でもさ、それって文句なしに罵倒をして、
But you know, wouldn't it be great to have a sexy and strict older sister...
ちょっとセクシーで厳しいお姉さんが最後よしよしするっていうのはありだよね。
...who scolds you without mercy but then comforts you at the end?
OK、OK、OK...
OK, OK, OK...
フブキちゃんが何かすごい青白い顔してるから、ちょっとここ秘密にしといて。
Fubuki-chan looks really pale, so keep this a secret for now.
そう、秘密、秘密、秘密。
Yeah, secret, secret, secret.
ちょっとYAGOOさんに、あのデ禁食らうかもしれないってなったら。
If Yagoo-san finds out, he might ban me.
やー、楽しみだなぁ！ASMRコラボができるって聞いたけど。
Man, I'm so excited! I heard we're doing an ASMR collab.
お待たせしました！
Sorry to keep you waiting!
あ、フブキちゃん！
Ah, Fubuki-chan!
よいしょ！待って...
Here we go! Wait...
耳増やしました！
I increased the ears!
気持ち悪い！！
That's gross!!
何これ？！わー、10個の耳で...
What is this?! Whoa, 10 ears...
10個の耳...
10 ears...
10個の耳でございます。
There are 10 ears here.
うお、これ誰の耳？わかんない、誰の耳なんだ？
Whoa, whose ears are these? I have no idea.
リスナーの耳かな？
Maybe they're the listeners' ears?
リスナーさんの耳かな？
The listeners' ears?
ちょっと増やしてみました。
I tried increasing them a bit.
いや、リスナーの耳だったらヤバくない？！
Wait, if they're listeners' ears, isn't that bad?!
「増やしてみました」って、10...え、5人ぐらいが犠牲になってるの？
You 'increased' them to 10... So five people were sacrificed?
そして、これもございます。
And we also have this.
うわ、耳生えてる！
Whoa, it has ears growing on it!
これはですね、あの「おみみくじ」という...
This is the 'Omimikuji' (Ear-Fortune)...
あ、「おみくじ」じゃなくて「おみみくじ」？
Not 'Omikuji', but 'Omimikuji'?
そう、横にお耳がついているおみ...
Yes, it has ears on the sides.
ま、年もね、明けたんですけど、パトちゃんも初詣とか行きました？
So, the new year has started. Did you go for your first shrine visit, Patra-chan?
いや、もうゲームしまくってて、ちょっと爆睡してたからさ。
No, I was playing games non-stop and then hibernated.
そう、全然行ってないんだよね。
I haven't gone at all.
そっかそっか。せっかくね、年始に入りますので。
I see. Since it's the beginning of the year...
ええ、おみみくじでですね、今年の運勢も占いながら遊んでいこうかなと思っております。
...I thought we'd play while telling our fortunes with this Omimikuji.
そうなんだ。え、あ、うん、ん？どういうこと？これはおみくじなの？
Oh, I see. Wait, what? Is this a fortune-telling thing?
おみみくじです。
It's an Omimikuji.
あ、おみみくじ。え、何もわかってないけど大丈夫かな？
Omimikuji... I don't get it at all, but is this okay?
まあまあ、大丈夫です。
It'll be fine.
それでは行ってみましょう！幸せボイス、ASMRお耳割り選手権！！
Well then, let's start! The Happy Voice ASMR Ear-Breaking Championship!!
いえーい！どんなタイトルやねん！
Yay! What kind of title is that?!
割るの？！
We're breaking them?!
はい、ASMRお耳割り選手権ですけども。
Yes, in the ASMR Ear-Breaking Championship...
ランダムに選ばれるテーマに沿ったASMRボイスで。
...we use ASMR voices that match a randomly selected theme...
あのあっちにありますね、10個のお耳たちを何枚割れるかを競うゲームとなっております。
...to see how many of those 10 ears over there we can break.
ASMRお耳割り選手権
テーマに沿ったボイスで何枚の耳を割ることができるかを競う
ASMR Ear-Breaking Championship
Compete to see how many ears can be broken with a voice matching the theme.
えっ、待って待って。素敵な、さっきASMRの良い話したのに割るの？！
Wait, wait! We were talking about how nice ASMR is, and now we're breaking them?!
はい、こちらのお耳を割ります。
Yes, we're going to break these ears.
割るの？！はい、え、割るの？！
Break them?! Wait, really?!
割れます、この耳。割れるの？！
These ears break. They do?!
この耳、ちょっと気持ちよくなると割れるらしいんですよ。
Apparently, these ears break when they start feeling good.
気持ちよく...ん？
Feeling good...?
「良いな」って思ったら、あの自らですね、弾け飛んでいくんですよ。
If they think 'this is nice,' they literally explode.
あ、へー、え、え、これあの、テーマに沿った素敵なボイスであればあるほどね。
Oh... So the more wonderful the voice matches the theme...
テーマにあった素敵なボイスであるほど多くの耳を割ることができる
The more the voice matches the theme, the more ears can be broken.
幸せになって昇天するという。
...the happier they get and then they 'ascend'.
昇天する？！え、すなわち、死...
Ascend?! You mean they die...?
また戻ってくるんで、はい。
They'll come back.
ちなみに素敵じゃないと、1枚も割れません。
By the way, if it's not wonderful, not a single one will break.
フブキさん、あのコメント欄が困惑してますけど大丈夫ですかこれ？
Fubuki-san, the chat is very confused right now. Is this okay?
合わせて大丈夫、大丈夫！みんなもよく推しのボイスで弾け飛んでるから大丈夫、大丈夫！
It's fine, it's fine! Everyone ascends with their oshi's voice anyway, so it's okay!
まあ、それはそうか。じゃあ大丈夫かな？
Well, I guess that's true. Then it's fine.
はい、そしてね、テーマを決めるのに使うのがこちらの「おみみくじ」！
And we'll use this 'Omimikuji' to decide the theme!
おおー！
Ooh!
まあ、細かい説明は置いときまして、出た結果によってあのテーマが決まるとだけ覚えておいてください。
I'll skip the detailed explanation, but just remember the fortune determines the theme.
わかりました！
Understood!
テーマはおみみくじの結果で決定
The theme is determined by the result of the Omimikuji.
はいはい、ではでは、ASMRの申し子パドちゃん、自信のほどはいかがですか？
So, Patra-chan, as an ASMR expert, how confident are you?
いや、やっぱりどんなね、テーマが来てもパトラはやり遂げてみせようと思うんですけど。
No matter what theme comes my way, Patra will see it through.
本当ですか？
Really?
そうだね。お参りの下り、全く関係なくなってるぞこれ。
Yeah. This has absolutely nothing to do with the shrine visit part anymore.
あるの？
Is there really a connection?
いや、大吉とかね、吉とか、最悪だと凶があるらしいんで。
There's Daikichi (Excellent Luck), Kichi (Good Luck), and at worst, Kyo (Bad Luck).
あ、凶あるの？！
Wait, there's Kyo too?!
そう、凶があるらしいです。そしてですね、ホロライブスタッフさんはね、よく遊び心満載なスタッフとしてですね。
Yeah, apparently. And the Hololive staff are known for being very playful.
ホロライブの中でもね、本当にもうバカ野郎みたいな、あのお題を出してくるので。
They come up with some really crazy challenges in Hololive.
パトちゃんもこの洗礼を受けていただきたいですね、ぜひ。
I'd love for Patra-chan to experience this initiation.
わかりました。
Understood.
じゃあまず白上からちょっと挑戦していきましょうかね。
Then Shirakami will go first.
それでは、おみくじ引かせていただきます。ガラガラガラガラ、よ！
Now, let me draw the fortune. Gara gara... Yo!
出てこい出てこい、おりゃ！
Come on out, come on out! Yah!
これは、あ、大吉！やったー！！
It's... Daikichi! Yay!!
ということでですね、え、大吉のテーマ、大吉デッキが多分出てくるかなと思います。
So, a theme from the Daikichi deck will likely come out.
出てこい大吉デッキ！
Come out, Daikichi deck!
来るかな？あ、来ました。
Will it come? Oh, here it is.
看護師さん
Nurse
これやるの？
Are you doing that one?
いや、こちらからですね、ルーレットが始まります。
No, from here, the roulette starts.
で、スタートって言ってストップで止まったあのテーマでASMRをしていこうかなと思います。
I'll say 'start' and then 'stop,' and I'll do ASMR with whatever it lands on.
おおー。ま、何が出るかは本当に運でございますね。
Ooh. So it's completely down to luck.
いや、看護師さんで良いと思いますけど。
I think Nurse is perfectly fine, though.
いやいやいや、別のになる可能性があります。
No, no, no, there's a chance it could be something else.
はい、ということで、じゃあ行きます。ルーレット、スタート！
Alright, here we go. Roulette, start!
何になります？
What will it be?
え、添い寝してくれる幼稚園の先生！
A kindergarten teacher who sleeps next to you!
添い寝してくれる幼稚園の先生
A kindergarten teacher who sleeps next to you
ありがとうスタッフ！バカ野郎のスタッフありがとう！
Thank you, staff! You idiots, thank you!
添い寝してくれる幼稚園の先生。
A kindergarten teacher who sleeps next to you.
全然変なテーマじゃないじゃん。
That's not a weird theme at all!
なんか、あれ？え、すごい、あれ...
Wait, what? Whoa, this is...
添い寝してくれる幼稚園の先生
A kindergarten teacher who sleeps beside you
大吉だ...
It's a great blessing...
大吉だからかもしれない。
Maybe because it's a great blessing.
あ、でも凶が出てたら多分やばかったと思う。
Ah, but if it was a curse, it probably would've been bad.
あ、そうなんだー。
Oh, is that so?
うわー、もう、添い寝してくれる幼稚園の先生かー。
Wow, a kindergarten teacher who sleeps beside you.
どんな感じのセリフなんだろう。
I wonder what kind of lines they'll be.
いやいやいやいや、もう何パターンも吹雪ちゃんと思いついてるから！
No, no, I've already thought of so many patterns for Fubuki-chan!
本当になーに？
Really, what is it?
はぁ〜、ありがとう、ママ。
Haa, thank you, Mama.
うわ、ママに！ママになるとのこと！？
Whoa, Mama! So you're becoming a Mama!?
ありがとう、ママ。なるほど。
Thank you, Mama. I see.
そうそう。
Right, right.
じゃあちょっと、白上ASMRやるので、パトちゃんフリだけをちょっとお願いしても、いいですか？
Well, I'm going to do Shirakami ASMR, so Patra-chan, could you please just do the lead-in?
じゃあこちらの、お耳さんたちですね。
Then for these ears over here.
はい！じゃあ、さぁ、行きますね。
Yes! Well then, here we go.
お願いします。
Please.
はい、吹雪ちゃんの、添い寝してくれる幼稚園の先生まで、3、2、1、どうぞ！
Okay, Fubuki-chan's "Kindergarten teacher who sleeps beside you" in 3, 2, 1, go!
よし、よし。早くねんねしようね。
There, there. Let's go to sleep soon.
ねんねしておきたら、いっぱい遊ぼうね。
When you wake up, let's play a lot.
あちちちちちちち...
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle...
[笑い声とうめき声]
[Laughing and groaning]
パトラ食べちゃう！
I'm gonna eat Patra!
おぎゃ、おぎゃ、おぎゃ、おぎゃ、おぎゃ、おぎゃ。
Waaa, waaa, waaa, waaa, waaa, waaa.
おギャーな吹雪。寝なさい。
A crying Fubuki. Go to sleep.
おっぱい、あ、うい。
Milk, ah, yes.
といった感じ、といった感じ、今の何割しましたか、こちら。
That's how it went. How many percent was that just now?
え、びっくりした、突然の「し」みたいな、そんな、えーっと。
Eh, I was surprised, like a sudden "shi", well...
1、2、3、4、5、6、7、7！
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, seven!
七パトラ出た！6...6人、6耳まで...
Seven Patras! Six... six people, up to six ears...
え、もう超良かったんだけど、え、吹雪、なんか...
Eh, that was just so good! Eh, Fubuki, somehow...
本当かな、白上が幼稚園の時に言われたやつや。先生に、先生にな。
Really? That's what I was told when I was in kindergarten. By the teacher, yeah.
尊い！
Precious!
え、尊い！
Eh, precious!
え、もう今のが聞けたから満足なんだけど！
Eh, I'm already satisfied just hearing that!
いや、もうやるんだよ！
No, you're doing it too!
あ、またやんの？
Ah, again?
そうだよ、次は、えー、パトちゃん、白上は七耳でしたけども。
That's right. Next is, well, Patra-chan, Shirakami had seven ears.
パトちゃんは一体どうなるんでしょうか。じゃあまずおみくじからですね。
I wonder what will happen for Patra-chan. Well, first the fortune slip.
あ、少しこれ、はーい。
Ah, a little bit of this, okay.
出てこい、出てこい。さて！
Come out, come out. Now!
なーんだ！
What is it!
これはなーに？
What is this?
お、吉！
Oh, a blessing!
吉！ということで、吉のトーク...テーマですかね。
A blessing! So, the blessing talk... theme, right?
はーい。
Yes.
テーマ。トークしちゃだめだ。テーマですね。出てくるかな？
Theme. I shouldn't say "talk". Theme. I wonder what'll come up?
吉は...お、雪の妖精！
The blessing is... Oh, Snow Fairy!
雪の妖精
Snow Fairy
雪の妖精！どこかわかんない。もうわかった。わきわからん。
Snow Fairy! I don't know where that's from. I get it now. I have no idea.
雪の妖精、わけわからん。
Snow Fairy, no idea.
そうそう。
Right, right.
まぁでもここからね、あの、スタートとストップ、パトちゃんお願いします。
Well, from here, Patra-chan, please do the start and stop.
はーい！ルーレット、スタート！
Okay! Roulette, start!
とらわれたお姫様
Captured Princess
ドゥルルルル...長いのがあるぞ。
Drrrrr... there's a long one.
ストップ！
Stop!
はずかし寝言
Embarrassing Sleep-talking
おお！はずかし寝言！なるほど。
Oh! Embarrassing sleep-talking! I see.
ちょっと恥ずかしい寝言、ってこと？
You mean like, a bit of an embarrassing sleep-talk?
だね。
Right.
ねー、はずかし寝言か。
Yeah, embarrassing sleep-talk.
恥ずかしい寝言かー。吹雪ちゃんなんか寝言で、こう言ってたよなって指摘されたことある？
Embarrassing sleep-talk... Fubuki-chan, have you ever been told you said something like that in your sleep?
本当ね。寝言、あの、友達の家に泊まり...
Really? Sleep-talk, when I stayed over at a friend's house...
した時に、あ、なんかね、うん。
...when I did that, ah, somehow, yeah.
「飛べない」って言ってたらしい。
Apparently I was saying "I can't fly."
「飛べない」！？
"I can't fly"!?
これめっちゃ覚えてることなんだけど。なんか、そう。
I remember this so clearly. Like, yeah.
「飛べない」って言ってたらしくて。
Apparently I was saying "I can't fly."
あ、何してた。夢全然覚えてないんだけど。
Ah, what was I doing? I don't remember the dream at all.
なんか「飛べない」って言ってたよ、吹ぶちゃんって言われて。
But I was told, "Fubu-chan, you were saying you can't fly."
「え！？」みたいな。
And I was like, "Eh!?"
何、バンジーか何かから飛ぼうとしてたのかなみたいな。そんな「飛べない」。
Like, was I trying to jump off a bungee jump or something? That kind of "can't fly."
寝言はちょっと恥ずかしいね、でもね。
Sleep-talking is a bit embarrassing, though.
なるほど。いや、可愛いな。
I see. No, that's cute.
いやいや、可愛くないよ。「飛べない」だよ？
No, no, it's not cute. It's "I can't fly", you know?
「飛べない」はさ。じゃあそんなパトちゃんは、思いつきましたか？
"I can't fly" is... Well then, Patra-chan, have you thought of something?
思いつきました！
I've thought of something!
けど、なんか今日はスタッフさんが、すごいいろんな道具を...
But, like, today the staff has provided so many different tools...
そうだ、そうだ。いろんな道具を、そう。
That's right, that's right. So many tools, yeah.
用意してくれたみたいで。ASMR用の道具が、道具がありますので。
It seems they prepared them. There are tools for ASMR.
ちょっとこれも使ってもろても、大丈夫なので。
So it's okay if I use these too.
でもなんかあの、すごいいろんなもの、歯ブラシとかあるんですけど。
But, like, there are so many different things, like a toothbrush.
シャカシャカしろってこと？シャカシャカしろ。
Does that mean "scrub-scrub"? Scrub-scrub.
寝言で使うの、それ？うーん、ちょっと。
Do you use that in sleep-talking? Hmm, a bit.
あと、謎の...
And also, a mysterious...
管内アナウンスかな？そういうのもありますね。
Is it an in-facility announcement? There are things like that too.
すごい。あ、いろいろね、アイテムございますが。
Amazing. Ah, there are various items.
はずかし寝言か。え、でもせっかくだからなんか使おうかな。
Embarrassing sleep-talk... Ah, but since I have them, maybe I'll use something.
これ、これ、どうやって使うんですか？
How do you use this, this one?
おさらみのおとお...
Sound of the... [mumbled]
あ、パトラ、やってた。
Ah, Patra was doing it.
あ、そうだった、憑依してた。
Ah, that's right, I was possessed.
じゃあ、何か寝言に使えるものあるかい？
Well then, is there anything I can use for sleep-talking?
何か寝言でしょ？寝言、どうぞ、どうぞ。
It's sleep-talking, right? Sleep-talking, go ahead, go ahead.
いや、わかんない。布みたいな、ないですね。
No, I don't know. There's no cloth-like thing.
布ないね。
No cloth.
じゃあ、ちょっと頑張って、そのまま行きますか？
Well then, should I just do my best as is?
はい、じゃあ行きますよ。
Okay, here I go.
それではパトちゃんのはずかし寝言、3、2、1、どうぞ！
Now then, Patra-chan's Embarrassing Sleep-talking, 3, 2, 1, go!
ふぅ〜。ふぅ〜。
Fuuh~. Fuuh~.
君のことが大好きなんだけど、吹雪、飛べない。
I love you so much, but Fubuki, I can't fly.
うぅ〜、飛べないの。
Uuuh~, I can't fly.
八耳割れ、おかしいだろ！
Eight ears split, that's just wrong!
やったー！ おかしいやんけ！
Yay! This is so weird!
おかしいやんけ！
This is totally weird!
やっぱりね、インタビューして、こうね、
As I thought, interviewing them and...
気持ちを聞いてやるっていうの大事かもしれないですね。
...hearing their feelings might actually be important.
刺さってましたよ。うん。
It really hit home. Yeah.
おお、やめろ、もうこれ、忘れるんだみんな。
Oh, stop it already. Everyone, forget this.
忘れろ、忘れろ。
Forget it, forget it.
あ、でもゾクゾクきましたって。
Oh, but they said it gave them chills.
あ、やったー。嬉しい、ありがとう。
Ah, yay! I'm happy, thank you.
そういうことでじゃあ、八を超えなきゃいけないのか。
So, I guess we have to top eight ears.
フブたちとかもね、なんか優しいよね。
The Fubus (fans) are really kind, aren't they?
ありがとう。
Thank you.
うみなーずも、そんな、もっと、もっと。
The Wuminas too, more, more!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
クソ、そういうことでちょっと、まだできるみたいなので、
Damn. So, it looks like we can do more...
白上行きたいと思います。
...so Shirakami will take a turn.
待って、チャットにもパトラの妹、
Wait, Patra's little sisters,
ふわもこちゃんが来てたって。
Fuwamoco-chan, were in the chat too.
妹になったんか？
They became your little sisters?
え、あ、違った？ 夢？ あれ？
Eh, oh, was I wrong? A dream? Huh?
うわー！
Whoa!
いっしょにたいよ。
I want to be with you.
サンキュー、サンキューふわもこ！
Thank you, thank you Fuwamoco!
うわー！
Whoa!
さっき見逃さなかった。ふわもこちゃんの耳も
I didn't miss that. I guess I have to heal
癒さなきゃいけないのか。
Fuwamoco-chan's ears too.
じゃあちょっと白上次行きますかね。またちょっと大吉とかがいいな。
Well then, Shirakami will go next. I hope for 'Great Luck' again.
はい。今日来い、今日来い、今日来い、今日来い。
Yes. Luck come, luck come, luck come, luck come...
うわー！ 凶だー！
Whoa! It's Bad Luck!
絶対やばいって！ 絶対やばいって、ホロライブ。
This is definitely bad! Definitely bad for Hololive.
なになになに。どうだったって？
What, what, what? What was it?
気になる。
I'm curious.
え、ちょっと、怖！
Eh, wait, scary!
今日のテーマじゃあ、ちょっと、出ますか？ 怖い、絶対やばい奴だ。
So, shall we see today's theme? Scary, it's definitely a bad one.
今の気持ちを5・7・5で
Express current feelings in 5-7-5
わけわかんないことさせるもん。もうわけわかんないことさせるんだから。
They make me do nonsense. They're always making me do nonsense.
5・7・5って。難しいことも他にもあるんだよね。うん。
5-7-5... There are other difficult things too. Yeah.
じゃあまあ行きますか、ルーレット、じゃあ。
Well then, shall we go? To the roulette, then.
はい。ルーレットスタート！
Yes. Roulette start!
だだだだだ... なんかやたら長くなるんですけど。
Dadadada... It's getting unusually long.
本当だ、めっちゃ長いの何これ。
It's true, it's really long, what is this?
ストップ！ べし！
Stop! Bam!
筋肉モリモリマッチョマンの変態になって一言
Say a line as a muscle-bound pervert
え、どういうこと？ 筋肉モリモリマッチョマンの変態になって一言。
Eh, what does that mean? 'Say a line as a muscle-bound pervert.'
困る、そういうこと？
I'm in trouble. Is that it?
ふー、待って、変態だよ？
Phew, wait, it's a pervert?
ふわちゃん、これご褒美じゃない。
Fuwa-chan, isn't this a reward?
ご褒美じゃねーよ！
It's not a reward!
いやー、これ筋肉モリモリがご褒美だよ。
No way, the muscle-bound part is the reward.
これはあの、映画のね、映画のコマンドーっていう映画に出てくる...
This is from that movie, the one called 'Commando'...
コマンドー。
Commando.
そう、あの...
Yeah, that...
シュワちゃんのことをね、警察官が、あの、筋肉モリモリマッチョマンの変態がいるみたいなことをね。
Schwarzenegger... there's a part where a police officer reports him as a muscle-bound pervert.
なるほど、なるほど、はいはい。通報する。
I see, I see, okay. Reporting him.
通報すること。白上これからシュワちゃんになるってことか。
Exactly. Does this mean Shirakami is going to become Schwarzenegger?
ムキムキになるってことか。よしじゃあ。
Going to become buff? Alright then.
どうしようかな。
What should I do...
楽しみ楽しみ、楽しみ楽しみ。
Exciting, exciting! Can't wait!
これ、いい感じかもしれない。
This might be good.
お、よいしょ。
Oh, heave-ho.
あ、何か道具を使うそうです。
Oh, she's going to use a prop.
皆さんにね見えないかもしれませんけど、ここにペットボトルのお水が。
You might not be able to see it, but here's a plastic bottle of water.
水、バキって言った。
The bottle went 'crack'.
おい、これに...
Hey, with this...
ふぅ。じゃあこれでいきましょうかね。
Phew. Then let's go with this.
一言。一言でいいんですよね。
A single line. One line is enough, right?
飛んで待ってたんだ。
I've been waiting.
よし、じゃあ。
Alright, then.
準備お願いします。
Please prepare.
はい！ それではフブキちゃんのコマンドーまで。
Yes! Then, Fubuki-chan's Commando...
3、2、1、ダダーン！
...3, 2, 1, Da-dan!
支えてるのは左手だ...
What I'm holding you with is my left hand...
利き手じゃないんだぜ。
...It's not my dominant hand.
利き手じゃないんだぜ、バキバキバキ。
It's not my dominant hand. *CRACK*
あ、耳の鼓膜が、また痛いね、鼓膜ね。
Ah, my eardrums hurt again. My eardrums.
ダダーン！
Da-dan!
全部いったね！ 全部いったよ！
You went all out! You went all out!
全部いったよ！
I went all out!
全部いった！
You went all out!
落ちちゃったね。うわー。
It fell over. Whoa.
落ちてたな。
It fell over, didn't it?
はいはいはい。
Yes, yes, yes.
完全に放してやったぜ。
I let him go completely.
いやさっきのうまかったね、そのペットボトルうまく利用して。
No, that was good earlier, using the plastic bottle so well.
バキバキ音をね、強い感じを出したりとか。
Using those cracking sounds to give a strong feeling.
そう。このシーンは、あの...
Yeah. This scene is the one where...
敵の人の足を掴んでさ、崖下にやってて。
...he's holding the enemy by the leg over a cliff.
はいはい、そう。今掴んでるのは、
Right, right. Saying, 'What I'm holding with now is...'
左手だ。利き手じゃないんだぜっつってそう。
...my left hand. It's not my dominant hand.'
え、ポルちゃんもだけどさ、ホロライブの子はみんなコマンドーのセリフも覚えてるの？
Eh, Pol-chan too, but do all the Hololive girls remember the lines from Commando?
コマンドーのセリフをね、そう。
The lines from Commando, yeah.
でもその後手を放すっていうね。崖下に落とすっていうね。
But then he lets go of his hand. He drops him down the cliff.
すごい。
Amazing.
そう。怖いシーンなんですけどもね。
Yeah. It's actually a scary scene, though.
いい作品なんでね、見てくださいね。
It's a great movie, so please check it out.
今ので癒されるのか。
Will people be healed by that?
いや、すごい。
No, it was amazing.
癒されたか分かんないけど、耳倒れたからね。
I don't know if they were healed, but the ears fell over.
耳倒れ、耳は倒れちゃったけどね。
The ears fell over, but yeah.
よいしょ。じゃあ続いていきますか。
Alright. Shall we move on to the next one?
パトラちゃんも。
Patra-chan too.
耳、耳復活してるってこと？
Does that mean the ears have been restored?
変えてくるの。よし行きます。
I'm changing it. Okay, here I go.
はい。お願いします。
Yes. Please go ahead.
おらおらおらおら！
Ora ora ora ora!
お。なんだ？ほ！
Oh. What is it? Ho!
吉！
Good Luck!
吉また！
Good Luck again!
なんなんだ！
What is it?!
ということでじゃあ吉のテーマ。
And so, the 'Good Luck' theme.
何が来ますかねぇ？
I wonder what it'll be?
はずかし寝言
Embarrassing Sleep Talk
さてさてさて。まず「はずかし寝言」がありましたからね。
Well, well. First we had 'Embarrassing Sleep Talk'.
寝言は来たからね。
Since 'Sleep Talk' came up.
じゃあルーレットどうぞ！
Then, roulette please!
ルーレットスタート！
Roulette start!
海の気持ち
The Sea's Feelings
え！海の...
Eh! The sea's...
これは...気持ち！
This is... feelings!
スバル！力をくれ！
Subaru! Give me strength!
スバル！
Subaru!
「海の気持ち」ということで。
So, 'The Sea's Feelings'.
えー、これね、海の気持ちってなんだ？
Eh, what exactly are 'the sea's feelings'?
これはもうさざ波の音以外ない。
It can only be the sound of ripples.
確かに。
True.
これは、そうだね、これを活用する...
That's right, utilizing this...
だけど「気持ち」だからね。気持ちも代弁しなきゃいけないよ、パトラちゃん。
But it's 'feelings'. You have to speak for those feelings, Patra-chan.
気持ちね。わかりました。
Feelings, huh. I understand.
いいですか？大丈夫ですか？
Are you ready? Is it okay?
わかりました。頑張ります。
I understand. I'll do my best.
はいはい。じゃあそんなパトラちゃんの「海の気持ち」まで。
Okay, okay. Then, leading up to Patra-chan's 'The Sea's Feelings'.
3、2、1、どうぞ！
3, 2, 1, go!
さざ波の音。
The sound of ripples.
君の気持ちも一緒にさらっていくよ。
I'll sweep your feelings away with me too.
おいしかったね。
That was good.
おいしかったです。
It was good.
さらわれろ！
Be swept away!
さらわれてよかっただろ。
It felt good to be swept away, right?
うわぁ！さらわれていったよ今。
Whoa! I was being swept away just now.
これが...スバルちゃんありがとう。
This is... Subaru-chan, thank you.
今スバルちゃんの気持ちを代弁したってこと？
Does that mean you just spoke for Subaru-chan's feelings?
いや、もうなんかずっとあの...さざ波の音が...
No, it's just, somehow, the sound of ripples was...
好きすぎて。
...something I liked too much.
好きね。
You like it, huh.
そうそうそう。ずっと頭にね、それだけあったんだよね。そう。
Right, right, right. That was the only thing in my head, you know? Yeah.
それを可愛く言ってみました。
I tried saying it cutely.
でも俺の知ってるさざ波と違う...
But it's different from the ripples I know...
これがさざ波かって。
...like, "Are these really ripples?"
そうです。これがさざ波です。
That's right. These are ripples.
いや...はい。でも一個ね、残ったのが悔しいです。
Well... yes. But it's frustrating that one remained.
そうだね。さらわれなかったやつがいるね。あいつちょっと強かったねあいつ。
Right. There's one that didn't get swept away. That guy was a bit strong.
敵討ってほしい。
I want you to finish it off.
じゃあもう一回じゃあ行きます。
Then, let's go one more time.
はい！じゃあもう一振り行きましょうか。
Yes! Then let's do one more shake.
ではでは。よいしょ。
Well then. Heave-ho.
今度は大吉になれ。大吉。
Become a 'Great Blessing' this time. Great Blessing.
よし。頑張れこの...！
Alright. Do your best...!
おいで、おいで！
Come here, come here!
出ただ！お、早い。
It came out! Oh, that was fast.
お！やった大吉だ！
Oh! Yay, it's 'Great Blessing'!
ということでじゃあ大吉のテーマ行きましょうかねぇ。
So, let's go with the 'Great Blessing' theme.
出るかな？
Will it come out?
添い寝してくれる幼稚園の先生
A kindergarten teacher who sleeps beside you
お、これさき...これさきのだってね。
Oh, this was... this was the previous one.
じゃあ行きましょう。ルーレットスタート！
Then let's go. Roulette start!
ルーレットスタート！
Roulette start!
女王様
Queen
女王様！
Queen!
うわぁ！楽しみだな！
Wow! I'm looking forward to it!
女王様...
Queen...
楽しみだなぁ。
I'm looking forward to it too.
女王様って何だ？
What is 'Queen'?
え、パトラ悪の女王だよ。
Eh, I'm the Evil Queen Patra.
え、おし...何を言ったらいいんです？
Eh, what... what should I say?
え、じゃあカメラさんちょっと下からいいですかね？
Eh, then, camera-man, can you go from below?
あ、そうそうそんな感じ。ほら！ほら！
Ah, right, right, like that. Look! Look!
ほら、ご褒美をあげましょう。このバカ犬！
Look, I'll give you a reward. You stupid dog!
みたいな。飲むでもいいし。
Like that. You can even drink it.
は、は、は...あり？あ、そのあとに。
Ha, ha, ha... Huh? Oh, after that.
ほら、上手く、よく泣けたわね。よしよしみたいな。
Look, you cried well. There, there, like that.
そういうのでもいいし。
That kind of thing is fine too.
風呂や！風呂や！ありがとうございます、女王様！
Bath! Bath! Thank you very much, Queen!
いいえいいえいいえ。これぞ...これぞ本気女王様。
No, no, no. This is... this is a serious Queen.
え、フブキちゃんの女王様楽しみだな。
Eh, I'm looking forward to Fubuki-chan's Queen.
ほら、なるほどな。ちょっとじゃあチクチク言葉みたいな...ってこと？
I see. So, like, some prickly words... is that it?
え、ご褒美じゃ。
Eh, it's a reward.
はい。この...このブタ...この犬...このバカ犬！
Yes. You... you pig... you dog... you stupid dog!
このバカ犬とか、あの「気持ち悪い」とかでもいいものね。
Like 'you stupid dog' or 'that's gross' would be fine too, right?
あ、そういうことね。うんうん。
Ah, I see. Yeah, yeah.
はい。じゃあちょっと頑張...ちょっと心苦しいが頑張るか。
Yes. Then I'll try... it's a bit heart-wrenching, but I'll try.
は...はい。なんて清らかな。
Ha... yes. How pure.
行きますじゃあちょっと清振りの。
Here I go, then, for the pure version...
はい！お願いします。
Yes! Please go ahead.
それではフブキちゃんのご褒美女王様まで。3、2、1、どうぞ！
Then, leading up to Fubuki-chan's 'Reward Queen'. 3, 2, 1, go!
このバカ犬。ちょっとも私の言うこと何にも聞かないんだから。けっし、けっし！ほら、喜べ。
You stupid dog. You don't listen to anything I say at all. Shoo, shoo! Come on, be happy.
この...変態！けっし！けっし！
You... pervert! Shoo! Shoo!
うわぁ、恥ずかしかったね。ありがとうございます！
Whoa, that was embarrassing. Thank you very much!
優しさがね、隠し切れてなかったけど、それはそれで良かったよ。
Your kindness wasn't fully hidden, but that was good in its own way.
うんうん。叩きながら...「うぅ...」って。
Yeah, yeah. While hitting... saying 'Uuu...'.
心...虫が...こうです。
Heart... insects... like this.
優しい。
Kind.
女王様殴りたくないですぅっていうフブキちゃんの優しさが...
Fubuki's kindness in saying "I don't want to hit you, My Queen"...
...なんかすごく良かったです！
...was really great!
女王様むずいわ。
Being a Queen is hard.
ちょっと、すぐに... すぐに憑依できなかった。
I couldn't... I couldn't possess the character immediately.
あー、でも、めちゃくちゃ良かったです。
Ah, but it was really good.
そんな感じが良かったです。
That vibe was great.
本当？
Really?
本当。
Really.
優しい女王様になるのだ。
You shall become a gentle Queen.
ということで、じゃ、パトちゃんも...
So then, Patra will also...
はい、じゃあパトちゃんの...
Yes, let's hear Patra's...
...女王様が聴きたいんだよな、もう一回な。
...Queen voice again.
パト？もう...
Me? Again...
...振られているわね。
...I'm being set up, aren't I?
じゃあ、いきます。
Okay, here I go.
はい。
Yes.
出てこい、出てこい。
Come out, come out.
出てこい。
Come out.
おっ？
Oh?
はい！
Yes!
おー、凶！
Oh, Bad Luck!
パトちゃん吉と凶しか出てないが。
Patra only gets Good Luck or Bad Luck.
本当だよー。
Truly...
本当、ということで、じゃあ今日の...
Really... so, for today's...
...テーマでお願いします。
...theme, please.
さっきね...
Just now...
筋肉モリモリマッチョマンの変態になって一言
Become a muscle-bound macho pervert and say a word
...「筋肉モリモリマッチョマンの変態になって一言」。
..."Become a muscle-bound macho pervert and say a word."
これさあ...
This is...
これ以外が来ると...
I wonder if something else will...
...思えへんのやけどこれ。
...ever come out.
もういいや。
Oh well.
じゃあ、ちょっとスタートとストップお願いします。
Then, start and stop please.
それでは...
Alright then...
スタート！
Start!
なんだ？なんだ？なんだ？
What is it? What is it?
ストップ！
Stop!
今の気持ちを 5・7・5 で
Current feelings in 5-7-5 syllables
「今の気持ちを5・7・5で」。
"Current feelings in 5-7-5."
むずっ、むずっ。
Hard, that's hard.
5と、7と、5。
5, 7, and 5.
え、待って、今の気持ちだよ？
Wait, my current feelings?
えーっと、今の気持ちでしょう？
Um, my current feelings, right?
うん。
Yeah.
わかった。
I got it.
いける？
Can you do it?
いけます。
I can.
すごい、早い！
Amazing, so fast!
うん。
Yeah.
さすがデッカクだから。
As expected of the Great One.
今の気持ちということで...
Since it's about my current feelings...
...鳴らしていこうかなと思います。
...I'll make them ring out.
鳴らしていく！？
Make them ring out!?
はい。
Yes.
じゃあ、いきますよ。
Okay, I'm going.
じゃあ、そんな、パトちゃんの...
Then, let's hear Patra's...
...今の気持ちを5・7・5で。
...current feelings in 5-7-5.
3、2、1、どうぞ！
3, 2, 1, go!
ホロライブ...
Hololive...
...これでいいのか...
...is this okay...
...スタジオは...
...for the studio...
ホロライブ (5)
Hololive (5)
これでいいんか (7)
Is this okay (7)
耳の中 (5)
Inside the ear (5)
大好きよ (5)
I love it (5)
ホロライブ様 (7)
Lord Hololive (7)
大好きよ (5)
I love it (5)
よし。
Good.
いやーーー！
Nooo!
えっ！？
Eh!?
それ、おかしくないですか？
Isn't that weird?
「これでいいのか」...
"Is this okay"...
...「大好き」という言葉で...
...and with the word "I love it"...
...耳が破壊されました。
...the ears were destroyed.
えー、えー。
Eh, eh.
なんかね...
You know...
...すごく、すごく単純な耳です。
...they are very, very simple ears.
さ、すごく単純なお耳でございました。
Indeed, they were very simple ears.
あー、ちょっと若干なんか...
Ah, I was a bit...
...ツッコミ調な口調で言っちゃったけども。
...using a bit of a "straight-man" tone.
うん。
Yeah.
「これでいいのか」。
"Is this okay?"
あ、またセットはね、ちょっと...
Oh, and the set...
...これじゃ良くない気がするんですけどもね。
...I feel like this isn't good.
もうスタッフさんがノリノリで作ってくれたのでね。
But the staff made it so enthusiastically.
うん、そうだね。
Yeah, that's true.
でも、ナイスな5・7・5でございました。
But that was a nice 5-7-5.
むずかしいや、これ。
This is hard.
いや、むずいよ、5・7・5。
No, 5-7-5 is hard.
じゃあ、ちょっともう一周で...
Then, let's do one more round...
...終わりにしましょうかね。
...and then wrap it up.
じゃあ白上、よし。
Okay, Shirakami's turn. Alright.
やったー！
Yay!
混ぜ、混ぜ。
Mix, mix.
えい、出ろ！
Ei, come out!
うぉー、これよ！
Whoa, this is it!
あら！
Oh!
出てこい、出てこい。
Come out, come out.
何だ？
What is it?
おー、吉！
Oh, Good Luck!
吉！
Good Luck!
吉は何があるんだ？
What's in Good Luck?
何だろう、何か...
I wonder... something...
...無難なものだと。
...standard.
無難なものでね...
Something standard...
...ネタはきっと入っていないと思うけども。
...I'm sure it doesn't have any joke prompts.
じゃあ吉のテーマお願いします。
Then, Good Luck theme please.
海の気持ち
The feeling of the sea
何だ？
What?
あ、よくないものだった、海の気持ちとか...
Ah, it was a bad one. "The feeling of the sea"...
...わけわからなかった。
...I didn't get it at all.
じゃあ、じゃあ、他行きますかね。
Then, let's go with another one.
どれと、スタート！
Here we go, start!
トイレのガマンが限界の時の心の声
Inner voice when you're at your limit holding back the bathroom
ストップ！
Stop!
えー！
Eh!
吉じゃん、これ。
It's a "Good Luck" one.
「トイレのガマンが限界の時の心の声」。
"Inner voice when you're at your limit holding back the bathroom."
すごいな、これはね...
Amazing, this is...
これ何だ？
What is this?
これはす、素晴らしい。
This is, wonderful.
なんか、一生聴けなさそうだし。
It feels like something we'll never hear again.
これ、ちょっと何かつかめるのか、これ。
Can I... can I grasp this?
トイレ我慢。
Holding back the bathroom.
あー、何も考えずにやるんだ。
Ah, just do it without thinking.
何も考えずに。
Without thinking.
それだけで俺たちは満足なんだ。
We'll be satisfied with just that.
な、なるほど。
I see.
我慢、よし。
Holding it... okay.
じゃあ、行きますか。
Then, shall we go?
心の声。
Inner voice.
はい。
Yes.
それでは、フブキちゃんが...
Alright then, Shirakami-chan's...
...トイレ我慢が限界の時の、心の中へ。
...inner voice when she's at her limit holding back the bathroom.
3、2、1、どうぞ！
3, 2, 1, go!
ひっ、ひっ、必死... 必死に...
Hi... hi... desperately... desperately...
...ひっ、ひっ、必死、必死に...
...hi... hi... desperately... desperately...
...ここ、これ、して... して...
...th... this... do... do...
んあーーー！
Nnn-aaah!
いや、これ全滅だろ！
No, that's a total wipeout!
全部破壊するのよ、今のは。
It destroyed everything just now.
弱いお耳でした。
They were weak ears.
いやー、素晴らしかった。
Wow, that was wonderful.
素晴らしかった。
It was wonderful.
あ、そんな感じかなと思って。
Ah, I thought it was something like that.
なんか新たな目覚めそう...
It's like something new is about to awaken...
おい耳が！耳が！
Wait, the ears! The ears!
すごいね。もう、破壊されてたのにギリギリに立ってたってことでしょ？
That was amazing. It means you were barely standing even after being destroyed, right?
あ、そういうこと。ギリギリで立っていた。
Oh, so that's what it was. Barely standing.
すごいね。もう耐えられなかったのか。
It was amazing. Maybe they couldn't endure it anymore.
いや、素晴らしかった。耳のトイレ我慢できなかった。
Yeah, it was wonderful. Could not hold the ear toilet.
え、可愛いし、恥ずかしがって一生懸命な感じがね、また良かったですね。
It was cute, and seeing you trying your best while feeling embarrassed was also great.
あ、そうなんですか。
Oh, really?
いや、もう、心の声って言ったら、もうたぶんそんな感じ、もうね、解放されたら、もう...
Yeah, if I were to speak from my heart, it would probably be something like that. If I had to let it out...
もう、一思いに解放してくれ！みたいな感じで。
...I'd be like, "Hurry up and set me free!"
ございました。
That's how it was.
素晴らしかった。
It was wonderful.
さてさて、最後、パトラちゃん、行きますか。
Now then, finally, Patra-chan, shall we go?
お願いします。
Please do.
そんなデカいハンマーくるか。ほら！
Coming at you with such a big hammer! Look!
なんだ？なんだ？
What? What?
ほらほら！
Here, here!
お？はい。
Oh? Yes.
どうして？！
Why?!
パトラちゃん、大吉出てないんだけど！
Patra-chan, it's not 'Great Blessing'!
どうして？！「凶」！
Why?! 'Bad Luck'!
おフブ様のせいでしょ！
This must be Fubuki-sama's fault!
ということで、今日のテーマはこちら。出てくるかな？
So, today's theme is this. Will it come out?
今の気持ちを5・7・5で
Express current feelings in 5-7-5
出てましたね。
It came out.
はい。
Yes.
じゃ、これ以外のものがきっと出てくれるはず。お願いします！
Then, something other than this will surely come out. Please!
ルーレット、スタート！
Roulette, start!
ストップ！
Stop!
かにかまとカニの会話
Conversation between imitation crab and real crab
待って！
Wait!
待って。え、
Wait, what?
待って、待って！何だ？！
Wait, wait! What's this?!
これがホロライブや。これがホロライブや。
This is Hololive. This is Hololive.
ああ、これがホロライブか。
Oh, this is Hololive.
すげーよ。
This is amazing.
パトラちゃんが一人二役ってこと？
So Patra-chan will play two roles by herself?
なーに。かにかまとカニの会話。
What? "Conversation between imitation crab and real crab"?
なんか可哀想になってきたから、どっちからやろうか？
I'm starting to feel sorry for them. Which one should I do?
え、やってほしい。両耳。
Oh, I want to do it! Both ears.
なんか可哀想だよこれ。
It's so sad.
どっちやる？どっちやる？
Which one should I do? Which one?
どっちが... かにかな、じゃあ。
Which one... imitation crab, maybe?
あ、じゃあ、かにかまする。
Then I'll do imitation crab.
おっけー、おっけー。
Okay, okay.
じゃ、フブキちゃんと一緒にやります。
Then, I'll do it with Fubuki-chan.
やりますか、これは。
Let's do this.
なんか使えるかな？何かカニっぽいのがあれば。
Can we use something? Anything crab-like?
カニっぽい？こういうの、カニっぽいかな？なんか。
Crab-like? Is this crab-like? Something like this?
あ、いいですね。
Oh, that's good.
なんか、この硬いところ使うとか。
Maybe use this hard part here...?
あ、カニ、こうやって。
Oh, crab, like this.
あ、それカクカク。あ、確かにカニっぽいかも。
Oh, that clicking sound, it's definitely crab-like.
はいはい、じゃあ、この辺で。
Okay, then let's go with this.
ちょっとあんまり近づきはできない。
We can't get too close.
じゃ、これ使おう。
Okay, I'll use this then.
はい。では、やります！
Yes. Well then, let's do it!
かにかまとカニの会話まで。
Conversation between imitation crab and real crab.
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, start!
カニ様...
Crab-sama...
私、かにかまなんですけど、もう、ぷにぷにすぎて、もうダメです。
I'm an imitation crab, and I'm so squishy that I'm already at my limit.
そんなこと、見て。
Look at me.
カチカチだよ。
I'm rock hard.
カチカチ... どうして君はそんな...
Rock hard... Why are you so...
私はそんなに柔らかい...
...and I'm so soft...
それは...
That is...
それは、パトラさんがぷにぷにいっぱいしてくれたからですよ。
That's because you've been squishing me so much.
でも、僕はカニだよ。
I'm a crab, you know.
知ってるよ。
I know.
ありがとう、フブキさん。こんなカオスなスタジオに寄ってくれて。
Thank you, Fubuki-san, for coming to such a chaotic studio.
一生忘れない... シュールな光景だよ、カニとカニカマ。
I'll never forget... It's a surreal sight, crab and imitation crab.
もっとそのカニのハサミで...
With those crab claws...
ちょん切ってください。
...please snip me.
あと、どうですか？
How was it?
ちょっと待って、待って！両耳ASMR！
Wait, wait, wait! Dual-ear ASMR!
なんかカオスなテーマでしたけど。
It was a chaotic theme.
カオスなテーマでしたね。
It was a chaotic theme indeed.
これは、これはね、シュールでとってもいい。
This was... this was surreal and very good.
これどうだったんですかね。
How was it, everyone?
なんか引きの絵があったらしいですよ。
Apparently there was a wide shot.
どシュールでした。
It was super surreal.
思ってたんと違うって？
It's different from what I expected?
でも、ナイス掛け合いだったよね。
But it was a nice banter.
まあ、確かにナイス掛け合いだったかもしれないですね。
Well, certainly, it might have been a nice banter.
ということで。
So...
はい。ええ、おみくじでございました。
Yes. So that was 'Omikuji'.
はい！皆さん、どうでしたか？これがASMRだ！
Yes! Everyone, how was it? This is ASMR!
まあ、あれだよね、やり方はいろいろあるよっていう。
Well, you know, there are various ways to do it.
そう。そう。
That's right.
すごくね、イチャイチャまったりしたものが聞きたい方は、ぜひ、フブキちゃんのASMRを加入してください。
For those who want to hear something more flirtatious and relaxed, please join Fubuki-chan's ASMR membership.
これよりすごく真面目にやらせていただいております。本当に、本当に真面目にやらせていただいております。
I perform it much more seriously than this. Really, really seriously.
パトラちゃんとまだやりたいことがなんか、ね。
Actually, there are still things I want to do with Patra-chan.
あ！ASMRだけじゃないということで。
Ah! It's not just ASMR?
あります、あります。
There are, there are.
何をやりたいんですか？
What do you want to do?
持ってきたんです。
I brought it.
何を持ってきたの？
What did you bring?
ちょっと待ってて。
Wait a second.
持ってくるから。
I'll go get it.
持ってくる？何を？
Get it? Get what?
え？もうお耳100億はここにあるというのに。
Eh? But 100 billion ears are already here.
よいしょ、よいしょ、よいしょ。
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho.
何何ちょっとちょっとちょっと何？
What, what? Wait, wait, wait, what?
フブちゃん持ってきた！お待たせー！
Fubu-chan, I brought it! Thanks for waiting!
えー！それってもしかしてパトちゃんの？
Whoa! Is that yours by any chance, Patra-chan?
そう！これ持ってきましたね！
Yes! I brought this!
持ってきちゃったの？今日。
You actually brought it today?
はい！FLX！
Yes! My FLX!
えー！かっこいいそれ！
Wow! That's so cool!
じゃ、これ本当にいつも弾いてるやつなんだけど。
So, this is the one I actually always play.
マジか！そうなんだ。
Really! Is that so?
そうなんです。今日はやっぱ、癒やしの配信って聞いてきたから...
It is. Since I heard this was a healing broadcast...
...この後癒やしの曲をね、ちょっと二人で歌いたいなって。
...I thought we could sing a healing song together later.
お、癒やしの曲！よ、よ...
Oh, a healing song! Yo, yo...
癒やしといえばさ、アコースティックギターとかじゃないの？
Speaking of healing, shouldn't it be an acoustic guitar?
これだって...
But this is...
あ、大丈夫大丈夫大丈夫。
Ah, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
アコギじゃないよね？
It's not an acoustic guitar, right?
これはね、バチバチのね、あのいい音がみんなの耳を幸せにするからね。
This intense and cool sound will make everyone's ears happy.
お、おかしいな。なんかそう、まったりした空間でね、アコギかと思いきやデレレレの...
That's odd. I thought it would be a chill acoustic sound, but it's like 'dererere'...
大丈夫、練習してきたから！
It's okay, I've practiced!
あ、本当？それで癒やしのやつ行けるのか...
Oh, really? And you can do a healing song with that...
そうだね！じゃあライブしちゃいますか！
Right! Shall we do a live performance then?
さぁ、お前ら！準備はできてるかー！？
Now, you guys! Are you ready!?
イエーイ！！
Yeah!!
お、癒やしの曲じゃない気がするな。
Oh, I have a feeling this isn't a healing song.
ま、いいや！それじゃあいっちょやりますかね！
Well, whatever! Let's give it a go!
イエーイ！！
Yeah!!
ということで、じゃあパトちゃんステージに移動だ！
And with that, Patra-chan, move to the stage!
癒やしパワー！！
Healing power!!
怖い！心配だ！
Scary! I'm worried!
俺たちの！魂の叫びを聞けー！
Listen to our! Soul's cry!
愛媛のみかーん！
Mandarins from Ehime!
みかん嫌いな奴いるけれど
Some people dislike mandarins
愛媛のみかんは一つだけ
But there is only one Ehime mandarin
愛媛のみかんを食べるなら
If you're going to eat an Ehime mandarin
心の愛を噛み締めろ
Savor the love in your heart
皮を捨てる奴がいる
There are people who throw away the peel
皮を捨ててはいけないぜ
You mustn't throw away the peel!
お風呂に入れてあったまれば
If you put it in the bath and warm up
ポカポカ
Warm and cozy
心がなごめば世界は一つ
If hearts are at peace, the world is one
世界は一つ
The world is one
世界にはばたけ 愛媛のみかん
Fly out into the world, Ehime mandarins!
みかん！みかん！みかん！
Mikan! Mikan! Mikan!
みかーーーん！
Mikaaaan!
愛媛のみかんは世界一
Ehime mandarins are number one in the world
みかんを体で感じよう
Let's feel the mandarins with our bodies
みかんを粗末にする奴は
Those who treat mandarins poorly
みかんにやられて死んじまえ
Will be finished off by mandarins and die!
こたつにみかんがない家は
A house with no mandarins on the kotatsu
日本の心をなくしてる
Has lost the heart of Japan
日本の心を取り戻せ
Retrieve the heart of Japan!
取り戻せ
Retrieve it
みかんを絞れ
Squeeze the mandarins
これがポンジュース
This is Pom Juice
命の水だ ポンジュース
The water of life, Pom Juice
みかん！みかん！みかん！
Mikan! Mikan! Mikan!
みかーーーん！
Mikaaaan!
みんなで飲もう
Let's all drink together
愛媛の心
The heart of Ehime
みかんを食えば
If you eat mandarins
救われる
You'll be saved
オレンジ巻き込み
Entrapping oranges
黄金色の果実
The golden fruit
命の雫だ
It's the drop of life
ポンジュース！
Pom Juice!
ミカ ミカ ミカン！ ミカ ミカ ミカン！
Mika-mika-mikan! Mika-mika-mikan!
ミカ ミカ ミカン！ ミカーン！
Mika-mika-mikan! Mikan!
ミカ ミカ ミカン！ ミカ ミカ ミカン！
Mika-mika-mikan! Mika-mika-mikan!
ミカ ミカ ミカン！ ミカーン！
Mika-mika-mikan! Mikan!
ということで、はい！みかんのうた！
So, that was "Mikan no Uta"!
いや、すごかったね！
Wow, that was amazing!
いや、楽しかったー！
Man, that was fun!
パトラがさ、めっちゃ回ってさ...
Patra, you were spinning so much...
やってたし、回ったとき見たときにさ、めっちゃ面白くて...
I was doing it, and when I saw you spinning, it was so funny...
すごかったね。笑いそうになりましたけども...
It was great. I almost burst out laughing...
皆さん、どう癒やしのライブだったでしょうか！
Everyone, how was that healing live performance?!
いや、もう最高だね。ホロライブスタジオ来たら...
Man, it was the best. Coming to the Hololive studio...
次ギターやりたくて...
...makes me want to play guitar next time...
いや、もうえぐかったギター！
Wow, your guitar playing was insane!
めっちゃかっこよかった！
It was so cool!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
素晴らしかったね。コメントでもすごい盛り上げてくれて...
It was wonderful. Everyone in the comments was getting so hyped...
ね。やっぱね、みんなね、ありがとう！
Right. Everyone, thank you so much!
みんな大好きみかんのうたでしょ。
Everyone loves "Mikan no Uta," right?
ポンジュースがバーンってね、吹き出ておりました。
The Pom Juice was just bursting out everywhere.
すごかった。
It was incredible.
いやー、素晴らしいライブでございました。ありがとうございます！
Man, that was a wonderful live performance. Thank you!
さてさて、えー、今回の3Dコラボのきっかけとなりましたですね、
Well then, the trigger for this 3D collaboration...
パトラちゃんプロデュースの白上のASMRボイスがですね、本日16時から発売になったわけなんですけども...
...was the Fubuki ASMR voice produced by Patra-chan, which went on sale today at 4:00 PM...
ちょっと改めてお知らせを...
Let me just share the announcement again...
あ、ごめん18時だ！18時！まだ早かった！
Wait, sorry, it's 6:00 PM! 6:00 PM! I was too early!
ちょ、暑い暑い！盛り上がりすぎちゃった！盛り上がりすぎちゃった！
Man, it's hot! I got a bit too excited! Too excited!
改めてね、お知らせもしておこうかと思います！
I'll share the announcement again properly!
はーい。いや、実はですよ。
Okay. Actually...
なんですか？
What is it?
もう、他のホロメンにも、こうパトラプロデュースのフブキちゃんのASMRボイスを、なんと！
I've already had other Hololive members listen to Fubuki-chan's ASMR voice, which I produced!
聴いてもらいました！
I had them listen to it!
聴いてもらってんの！？一番聴かれたくなかったのに仲間にー！
You had them listen to it?! They're the ones I least wanted to hear it!
いや、もうパトラがちょっと、これお願いしてね。
Well, I asked them to do it.
聴かないでー！
Don't listen!
レビューを書いてもらいました。
And I had them write reviews.
レビュー！？ちょっとどんな風に来てんのか恥ずかしいですね。
Reviews?! Man, that's embarrassing. I wonder what they said.
では、ままま、まずはね、ちょっと先に、お知らせしていこうと思います！
Well, first off, let's go over the announcement!
お知らせこちらです！ダダダーン！
Here's the announcement! Ta-da!
本日ですね、白上フブキ「白狐のおもてなし宿」ASMRボイスが発売となりました！
Today, Shirakami Fubuki's ASMR voice "White Fox's Hospitality Inn" has been released!
かわいいー！
So cute!
ありがとうございます。えー、シナリオと監修はですね、もうパトラちゃんがもう本当にすべて担当してくれております！
Thank you. Patra-chan handled everything, from the scenario to supervision!
収録もパトラちゃんのあのスタジオの、もう本当にいいマイクといい設備でね、経由100で撮っておりますので...
We recorded it at Patra-chan's studio using really great microphones and equipment...
もう本当にハイクオリティなものとなっております！
...so it's a very high-quality product!
よろしくお願いします！
Please check it out!
フブキちゃんのね、いろいろな声が聴きたいから、シチュエーション別でこう3つボイスをね、作らせていただきました。
I wanted to hear various voices from Fubuki-chan, so I made three different situation-based voices.
恥ずかしい...
So embarrassing...
もう1個からでも購入ができるというね。
And you can purchase them individually.
そうなんですよね！はい、まあ気になったシチュエーション聴くもよしだし、もちろん全部聴くもよしなんですけども、
That's right! You can listen to the ones that interest you, or of course, listen to all of them.
こちら全部聴くと大体45分弱ぐらいある、本当に長いASMRとなっております。
If you listen to everything, it's nearly 45 minutes long. It's a very substantial ASMR.
30分ぐらいって言われて、なんか作ったらね、結構なっちゃったっていう感じでね。
I was told to aim for 30 minutes, but once I started making it, it ended up being that long.
あ、もうめちゃめちゃオーバーしてるけど、もう二人の本当に大サービス！大サービス！大サービスでお届けしております！
It's way over, but it's a huge service from both of us! We're delivering it as a major treat!
そしてですね、フルセットご購入いただけますと特典がございます。
Also, there's a bonus if you purchase the full set.
まずはこちらのPC壁紙！
First is this PC wallpaper!
かわいいー！ななこ先生に...
So cute! By Nanako-sensei...
描き下ろしいただきましたー！
I got a special illustration!
お隣の白狐お姉さんやあ。
It's the Shirogitsune big sister next door.
かわいい！
So cute!
この雰囲気がそのままASMRのシチュエーションボイスになっておりますので。
This atmosphere is exactly what the
ASMR situation voice is like.
デスクトップにしていただいて、ちょっと聞いていただければなと思っております。
I hope you set it as your desktop
and give it a listen.
イラストの構図とかもね、あの、リクエストして、頼んでいただいたんです。
I even made requests for the
illustration's composition.
パトちゃん、ありがとうございます！
Patra-chan, thank you so much!
でも、こういうシーンがあるということでですね。
So it's a scene like this.
さてさて、そして、そして！アフタートークボイスも付いております！
And there's more! An aftertalk
voice is also included!
こちら、本当にボイス収録の直後に、パトラちゃんとね、お話しさせてもらいまして。
Right after the voice recording, I got
to talk with Patra-chan.
こちらも超良いマイク、KU100で収録しておりますので。
We recorded this with a super
high-quality KU100 mic.
もう、本当自分でも言うのも何なんですけど、めちゃめちゃ豪華な特典なんじゃないでしょうか。
I shouldn't say it myself, but isn't
this a super luxurious bonus?
はい、パトラちゃんのね、ボイス収録後の生のガチの感想も聞けてますので、皆様ぜひともよろしくお願いします。
You can hear Patra-chan's raw, real impressions
after the recording, so please check it out.
白上フブキ「白狐のおもてなし」ASMRボイスは、ホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップでご購入いただけます！
Shirakami Fubuki's "Shirogitsune Hospitality"
ASMR voice is available at the Hololive shop!
特に期限は書いてなかったり。こちら、期間限定とかではないっぽい。
No specific deadline is mentioned.
It doesn't seem to be a limited-time offer.
白上があまりの恥ずかしさに「すみません、販売停止にしてください」って言わない限りは。
Unless I say "Please stop selling this"
out of sheer embarrassment.
そしたらパトラが「じゃあ、もう一回、あの、販売開始してください」って言えば。
In that case, if Patra says
"Please start selling it again"...
あー、それは助かる！パトちゃんが言った。
That would be a lifesaver!
Patra-chan said it.
大丈夫かな。なので、急がなくても大丈夫です。
I wonder if it'll be okay. So,
no need to rush.
はい。頑張って録ったので、皆様よろしくお願いします。
I worked hard on the recording,
so please, everyone.
はい！はい！それでは！
Yes! Yes! Now then!
レビュー、レビュー行くか。
Shall we go to the reviews?
うわー！緊張する。やめよー。
I'm nervous. Let's not.
みんなだって！ホロメンには聞かれたくなかったのにー！
I didn't want the Hololive
members to hear it!
だって、めっちゃ恥ずかしいよ！ホロメンだ。
It's so embarrassing! It's Hololive members.
だってレビューを、早速見てみましょう。
Let's check out the reviews right away.
ウソ！怖ーい。怖ーい。
No way! Scary. Scary.
何て言われてるの。
What are they saying about me?
それでは私、読み上げさせていただきます。
Well then, I shall read them out.
はい！まず誰からですか？
Okay! Who is the first one from?
まずタイトル。「そばにいるよ！フブキがそばにいる！」
First, the title. "I'm here! Fubuki is right here!"
これ誰だよ。
Who is this?
FLUFF & FUZZさんからのレビューです。
It's a review from FLUFF & FUZZ-san.
え？フワモコちゃん、もしや。
Wait, Fuwamoco-chan, perhaps?
「最高でした！フブさんの隠れ家にお邪魔しました。」
"It was the best! I visited Fubuki-san's hideout."
「耳が幸せすぎて、ずっと脳みそがとろけちゃいそうでした！」
"My ears were so happy, my brain
felt like it was going to melt!"
「脳みそがとろけることなんて、こんなに気持ち良かったんだ…！」
"I didn't know brain-melting could
feel this good...!"
「一日終わりのご褒美になっています。天才！バウバウバウバウ！」
"It's my end-of-day reward.
Genius! Bau bau bau bau!"
フフ、フワモコちゃんじゃねーか。
Hehe, it's Fuwamoco-chan.
ということなんですよ。本当に聞かれてんの、ウワア。
So that's how it is. They really heard it, waaah.
はい、FLUFF & FUZZさんですけど、フワモコちゃんですね。
Yes, FLUFF & FUZZ-san is Fuwamoco-chan.
さっきもね、コメントいっぱいしてくれたんですけど、ありがとう。
They gave me lots of comments earlier too, thank you.
お姉ちゃん頑張ったよ。変質者だけど、頑張ったよ。
Big sister did her best. I was
a creep, but I did my best.
いや、まだあります。
No, there's more.
まだあるの。誰だよ他に聞いたの。
There's more? Who else heard it?
「なんだこれ…癒されるだけじゃねえね…」
"What is this... it's not just healing..."
チョコタロウさんのレビューです。
It's a review from Chokotaro-san.
チョコ先生！仲良いんですよね、チョコタロウさん。
Choco-sensei! You're close, aren't you, Chokotaro-san.
トラック1の感想は「白狐の隠れ家」。
Impressions of Track 1: "Shirogitsune Hideout."
「触っていいですよって照れながら言う感じが可愛くて、中二心がぶっ刺さり心臓掴まれました。」
"The way she shyly says 'You can touch me' was so cute, it
pierced my inner middle schooler soul and grabbed my heart."
「耳温めてくれるのが吐息で温めてくださって、一生懸命してくれる姿が想像できて、ドキドキした。」
"The way she warms my ears with her breath, I could imagine
her working hard and it made my heart race."
「温かい気遣ってくれる言葉と一緒に撫でてくれるので、心まで温かくなれるボイスでした。」
"Because she strokes my head with warm, caring words,
it's a voice that warms the heart."
いや、すごいです。チョコ先生、ありがとうございます。
Wow, this is amazing. Choco-sensei, thank you.
あのね、分かりみがあるんだよね、チョコ先生。
I can totally relate, Choco-sensei.
トラック2「お耳マッサージ」、お茶を作ってる音とゆっくり喋ってくれる癒しボイス。
Track 2 "Ear Massage," a healing voice talking
slowly with tea making sounds.
「聞いてるとほっこりしてきてからの、距離がどんどん近くなってドキッとした。」
"Listening to it makes you feel relaxed, then the
distance suddenly gets closer and it made me jump."
「そして、マッサージの音もどんどん刺激的になってくる感じが、とても良かったです。」
"And the massage sounds getting more and more
stimulating was really good."
「オノマトペも癒し、ウィスパーボイスで心地よくて、ずっと聞いていたくなるボイスでした。」
"The onomatopoeia is also healing, and the whisper voice is
so pleasant that it's a voice you want to listen to forever."
お山作ってるけど。
She's making 'mountains' though.
素晴らしいレビューですね。
What a wonderful review.
「音がどんどん刺激的になってく感じと、フブキちゃんが優しくなってく感じを、読み取ってくれるんだね。」
"She really picks up on the sounds getting more
stimulating and Fubuki-chan getting gentler."
チョコ先生、めっちゃ聞きすぎや。ガチガチのレビューだよ。
Choco-sensei, you've listened to it way too
much. It's a hardcore review.
フルセット購入特典
キービジュアルPC用壁紙
白上フブキ「白狐のおもてなし」ASMRボイス
Full Set Purchase Bonus
Key Visual PC Wallpaper
Shirakami Fubuki "Shirogitsune's Hospitality" ASMR Voice
フルセット購入特典
アフタートークボイス
出演：白上フブキ、周防パトラ
Full Set Purchase Bonus
Aftertalk Voice
Cast: Shirakami Fubuki, Suou Patra
チョコ太郎さんは...
Choco-taro says...
03. 楽しそうに耳かきをしてくれている感じから
03. From the feeling of her happily cleaning my ears,
だんだんと小悪魔な感じを出してきて
she gradually starts showing a little devilish side,
耳かきで気持ちよくさせられながら
and while being made to feel good by the ear cleaning,
手の平で転がされる感じが たまりませんでした！
the feeling of being played with in the palm of her hand was irresistible!
「コロコロ」っていうね。
"Rolling around," huh?
白上フブキちゃんのトリコになる...
Becoming captivated by Fubuki-chan...
トラックですね、これは。
That's what this track is about.
（恥ずかしがる声）痒い... 全身痒い...
(Embarrassed noises) It's so itchy... My whole body is itchy...
どうしたの？
What's wrong?
痒い！
It's embarrassing!
ちなみにアフタートークの感想まであるんですけど。
By the way, there's even a review for the after-talk.
痒いよ～...
It's too much...
アフタートークに感想ってすごいですね。
A review for an after-talk? That's amazing.
すごい、アフタートークもしっかり聴いて...
Wow, they listened carefully to the after-talk too...
「左からフブキ様の声、右からパトラ様に挟まれて...」
"Sandwiched between Fubuki-sama's voice from the left and Patra-sama's from the right..."
「お耳が幸せで、お二人のてぇてぇに挟まれて...」
"My ears were in heaven, and being between the two of you was so precious..."
「耳がいい意味でくすぐったかったです！」
"My ears were ticklish in a good way!"
痒いよ～...
It's so embarrassing...
すごいね。俺たちの感想くれて。ありがとうございます。
That's great. Thank you for giving us your thoughts.
ガチですね...
You're a real fan...
こういうのいるよね、そういうサイトとかでしっかりレビューする人。
There are people like that, right? Who write detailed reviews on those sites.
震えるサイトとかね。
On those specialized sites.
そうね、すごい。
Yeah, it's impressive.
でもそれだけしっかりとチョコさんも聴いてくれたということで。
But it means Choco-san listened that carefully.
すごいですよ、もう。
It's really amazing.
チョコさんにどんな顔して会えばいいんだ...
I don't know how I'll look Choco-san in the eye...
フワフワさんも、チョコ太郎さんも、星くんも、星...
Fuwafuwa-san, Choco-taro-san, Hoshi-kun, Hoshi...
星、星が... めちゃくちゃ高評価、高評価ですか？
The stars, the stars... Is it a really high rating?
はい、ありがとうございます。
Yes, thank you so much.
いや、他の裏面は聴かないで。本当に聴かないでください。
No, don't listen to the other hidden tracks. Please don't.
全員聴いてほしい！
I want everyone to listen!
聴かないでください、本当にお勧めしない。表、表みんなも。
Don't listen, I really don't recommend it. Just the main ones!
お耳がイボイボしてきて...
My ears are getting all tingly...
可愛いよ～、可愛いよ～。
It's so cute, so cute.
やめろー！ こりゃー！
Stop it! Cut it out!
やめろ、これ！
Stop this!
良いパンチだぜ、フブキ。
That's a good punch, Fubuki.
うわ～... あ、と、と、と...
Whoa... Ah, and, and, and...
ということで、お二人だけですか？ よかった、よかった。
So, it was just the two of them? Good, good.
いや～、もう高評価でよかったです。
Well, I'm just glad for the high rating.
めちゃくちゃ高評価でしたね。
It was a really high rating, wasn't it?
でもレビューしてくれたワオちゃん、そしてチョコさんも、ありがとうございました！
But Wao-chan and Choco-san, who gave us reviews, thank you so much!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
でもレビューを聴いてちょっと気になった、そこの君！
And you there, who got curious after hearing those reviews!
うん！
Yeah!
ぜひともパトラちゃんとプロデュースしてくださった、渾身の作品なので、聴いてみてください！
It's a masterpiece produced with Patra-chan, so please give it a listen!
聴いてください！
Please listen to it!
ま、本日はですね、いろいろなやかんやってきましたけど、パトちゃん、いかがでしたか？
Well, we've done all sorts of things today, but Patra-chan, how was it for you?
いや、今日は、なんか来た瞬間カオスな...
Well, today, from the moment I arrived, it was chaos...
お耳いっぱいの、中、迷い込んだから、なんか来る場所間違ったかなと思ったんですけど。
With all the talk about ears, I thought maybe I'd come to the wrong place.
はいはい。
Right, right.
やっぱね、あんなになんかもう、ポンジュースが吹き出るライブもさせてくださいましたし。
But you know, you even let me do a live performance where orange juice was spraying everywhere.
そうだね。
That's true.
何よりパトラが一生懸命プロデュースしたフブキちゃんのボイスをこんなに「痒いよ～」とか言ってくれたんで、
More than anything, since you reacted with things like "it's embarrassing" to the voice track I worked hard to produce,
めちゃくちゃ幸せなんで満足です。ありがとうございました！
I'm incredibly happy and satisfied. Thank you so much!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
新年いい思いしました。
I had a great start to the new year.
おみくじ凶ばっかだったけど。
Even though I kept drawing bad luck at the shrine.
きっと今年一年もいい年になるよ、パトちゃん！
I'm sure this will be a great year, Patra-chan!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ということでね、本日のコラボはここまでです！
And with that, that's it for today's collaboration!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
モフモフ！ モフモフ！
Fluff fluff! Fluff fluff!
うわ～やめろー！
Whoa, stop it!
モフ！ モフ！
Fluff! Fluff!
やめろ、やめろ！ やめろ！ やめろ！ おらー！
Stop it, stop it! Stop! Stop! Take that!